From the shadows of the subconscious, to the chaos of the cosmic scrolls, this is Psyche Awakens.
Crowd, whoosh, sparkly chimes, thundercrack.
You smooth mystical.
Yo, welcome to the madness, buckle in tight.
Tarot on deck, third eye in flight.
True skit told he goes unfold.
dropping spirits in the chat and the vibes ain't stopping linoa's on guard tricks bringing love
lola rooty marbles fan from above it's like we awake and step in the flame we call your truth
we say your name it's wow that's real it's so big play now grab your tea and slay the dead
it's like we awake hands don't look away your shadows talking it came to stay we laugh we
Hi, baby. Hi, you came over, came over to say hi.
Hello.
Hi. Thank you. Thank you so much.
Hmm. Okay. I'm married. Thank you for coming. Thank you.
Hi,
Tonya. Sorry, do I know your um,
by another name, because sometimes it's changed a little. You're welcome.
I'll slowly start
adding some back.
People that I've noticed have my back in places
But I don't want to miss anything. Okay
Did I know you're going to be in the chat Jen hold on I
Did not I did not what did you uh like that?
Maybe I did maybe I did you hear me, okay? Okay. Sorry if I
Hello
You're here
Holy hi
Jen about it, what's your that's your other name like it's hard to tell the you know, they changed all these names around in my shot
I don't know why they did that
But it was, it was kind of a crazy, crazy night.
I got like a headache from yelling so much
and I don't, I hate yelling.
And it's just like, but also like, I was, you know,
some people were yelling in my ears
because I have a, my headphones in
and they're like really loud.
So you don't need to yell, but I was, I don't know.
But thank you.
people that yelled at me. Give me a little bit of a headache. I'm probably not here. Okay.
Hi, babe.
I don't like streams like I had earlier where I'm just like
Venting
But and I don't want to like bent on on you guys
Supposed to be
I'm supposed to be healthy, right? Oh, I am. Hi, babe
Hi, are you over there?
It's Lenore inside Lenore was inside too
Aw, then thank you, Jamie. I know Jamie made me some cute graphics and stuff. Thank you, Jamie.
Okay, so, let me see if I can fix this.
Sorry.
Oh my gosh.
So good.
Yeah, I will. Oh, thank you so much.
No
There we go
Hi Christine
Yeah
It's been a roller coaster. It's been a roller coaster
But you know, it's like it's a negative
Negative shows and I had some like super really really positive shows too. I even had great shows yesterday
And it's like, it's just crazy.
Hi, Christine.
How are you?
Oh, I'm sorry, here.
You have the doctors?
You know, last night I unmodded everybody
so I could start over because,
so it's like if you're not feeling.
no one be offended or anything it was just like I decided to do it everybody because
look you're doing good Christine um let's see
yeah I had fun some fun last night like I was like at betas um I went in like just like let me
Makeup for some people, right?
I tried I tried I was think I was successful with one person high time I was successful with the person I
think this guy clumsy
And I got to work things out the rest of the people I
Was sometimes worse successful than other times
It was fun, but some of it was fun, but then it's like, you know, when it got to like,
you know, it was really hard to talk sometimes, and get my point out, and it's like, I don't
know, I do feel misunderstood sometimes, and I'm not trying to like, I want to be, I want
wanted to be good um but it kind of like went off the rails like things do sometimes
but
I don't know if I made a better move so I'll hang out for a while yeah and it's like I
and I do take a lot of feedback seriously like you know
People might wonder why oh what like why doesn't that why isn't there very much tarot on the show well guys?
I actually I've gotten good news. I think I'm on my one thousand
One thousand
Tiktok subscriber. What is your shows have to turn into shit because you don't care
Why does my shows have to turn to shit?
Hi, thank you
I don't care. Oh, I do care. I cared a little bit too much. I don't know. I think I care not too much.
You can't care. I can't care enough, but I do care. And I hope the show's not turning to shit.
But yeah, some people are wondering, why don't I do very much tarot on the show?
and then I'm sorry if I uh hold on a minute
so to make sure I got everything
uh-oh I blame you I don't think I blame you maybe you know I did I'm sorry
um other people's opinion it would opinions are one thing it's like being like people screaming in my ear
Like and I didn't come to like fight. I didn't I didn't I didn't come saying I want to fight
I want to like, you know, blah blah blah
It's like I didn't if I came in that spirit, but I understand like but I ended up like, you know
I ended up yelling I got a headache and stuff. I don't blame you. I love you, sweetheart
I really love you and it's not
If I blame you, I'm sorry, you know, I don't think I did but
I'm sorry if I did
No, you're not a bad guy. You're not a bad guy. Just hold on a second. I'm not. Hold on a second. I've modded everybody. Okay, hold on. I have to reach to do it. You're not a bad guy somewhere. You're not a bad guy.
I always feel bad after, I don't like to get in my skin, but it's like I did, not by you necessarily, it was somewhere, it was before that, it was like other stuff, and then it was like, okay, so I do have apologies, I'm sure, it's like, you know, I know, I know I'm not perfect.
But I don't think I really don't think I ever came in the spirit of like
Meanness like the others because of explanations. There's reasons. There's logic that makes sense to me behind
Some things I do or can say and things like that that might not be clear everybody
It's hard it's hard and I know and especially
Content creators, you know, and I know there's like you know, some words a great content creator
I mean, yeah, she's above, um, Bita, um, and I really, I consider other content creators
colleagues that I don't want to fight with any of them, and it's like, and I feel bad,
and also it's like, kind of, I wish I was on for, like, able to go on other shows
more, right? Um, but just like, things happen, like, and it's not anybody's
It's not necessarily that far, it's too, it's like, it's hard, but uh, it's like a lot of people,
a lot of opinions, a lot of, I don't know, I just feel like people get mad at me sometimes,
and it wasn't like my intention to like make anybody mad or to like...
I'm very heart on my sleeve very emotions on my sleeve. I'm not trying to play a victim. I swear
I'll think responsibility. I'll think responsibility. Yeah, I'm not pale sometimes. Okay
Absolute I can be a mess. I
Don't know
I've started an emergency live while you were live are you talking about last night?
Yeah, I have, but it's because I need to say my side and I felt like I couldn't say I was not able to communicate.
I was like, I don't like to interrupt people.
And it's like, and then when I was, I was getting out of my...
Calm center
Being I came to have fun. I really did I and I did I had so much fun when I we were doing the chat
She'd be tea like you know
Stuff and like laughing and when that guy with the drums came on and
I was having so much fun and it's like and I was ignoring the chat
And I was I was I tried I tried I failed I failed sometimes I do fail
Sometimes I need time, sometimes I need to vent and it's not anything, I wasn't trying
to take anything away from you and I think every time I, I hope I did, you know, I've
been, tried to, thought I tried to like say I love people, I didn't, I'm sorry, okay?
I can't help being sensitive, like, and you know, I'm an empath, I am really, I'm very
sensitive to negativity, and it's like, and I get kind of a lot of it, and it's not anybody
in particular, but it's like a lot of things at once, and sometimes it's like, and then
I don't like to yell, I feel bad, I don't like to try to talk over people, I don't like
I'm not perfect so I don't mean it I don't want to like
Wasn't an emergency life about you. It was about me. It was about me trying to express myself, okay?
so I
Didn't totally I didn't clear my ban list. I actually cleared all my lists
I took every I cleared all the mods. I clear all the ban list. There's zero people in the ban list zero
Again, I did it. You know, maybe a dumb idea because it's like most the people should have been there, but
Okay, okay
Whether I take hide somebody or not they're gonna come back. It's like what can I do? I'll come back to you know five five people, right?
so
Yeah, and then Jamie understands that right, you know and like having like
you know
Michael passed away
I'm trying to fix things that I'm trying to fix things I can't I
I all I believe in miracles. Well, I got McDonald's coffee. Oh
Jamie I
Know life can't change it instant, right?
and
Wow
It's like, I don't want to, I don't want to leave on bad, I don't want to leave the earth or anybody to leave the earth on bad, on bad terms.
Or was like the last thing said, being negative, especially me.
It's like, really, I didn't come in with the spirit of like, I did come with the spirit of love.
That's what I came in with.
I didn't come in with the spirit of opposition and defiance and anger or blah, blah, blah, blah.
Okay.
But I hope people will stay for a second and like before like, you know
Just say oh, I'm not a mod that he said fuck me. It's like cuz I'm remodding but I just I just cleared all the list
I just I just needed a reset
reset, but I'm rebuilding back up, right
Thank you
Everyone's free, Jim. There's not one BAM person. Yeah, I don't know some are left or some are here. I'll let you some
I'm sorry
Sorry, things went off the rails. I'm sorry if I
Got oversensitive, right?
Bro me and I sometimes I need to know
Your other name if I if you have a different name
I can just tell me like what I know you as if it's a different name. Okay, so make sure I got it
I still want everybody, even people that don't like me,
I want them to be able to promote.
Okay, even if I don't make them a mod,
I do want them to let a mod know their channel.
If they're trying to promote, if they're trying to get started,
I really want to build a community.
I really want people to be successful in the community,
whether they just want to have fun
or whether they want to do something
to make a little extra money or whatever, it's like,
but...
No, I'm not going to be getting a part-time job because this is my full-time every tick right now.
And so, whether it makes money or not, you know, I've survived on a, I've survived so far.
Okay, well, I do, I can't really see it, little writer, but tell me who you are,
see, I don't know who everybody is, because I just want to make sure if I,
if I know you by a different name, just let me know who you are, okay?
There's no link yet. Just give me a minute. I'll put a link up. Hold on.
Okay, let's see.
Yeah, I don't and I don't want to hurt anybody's feelings. I think yeah, it looks like it looks like I've pissed people off already.
I'm here to talk.
But I came back.
I'm also like, I don't...
I'm not gonna give up on people either, but there's nobody banished him. I can't I can't tell you
Everybody is unblocked everybody. There's not one block person
You know it's like
and you know what
I'm not mad at anybody. I'm not mad at myself for a lot of things
I'm harder on myself than people are and it's like if you can imagine
If you can imagine, the people are hard on me, but I'm harder on myself.
And I'm like, I didn't, I always feel like, or not feel like, I, you know, it is, yeah,
you're free.
I told you I'd unblock everybody.
Yeah.
What is that, a panda?
I'm not I'm not singling anybody out like or being sarcastic. I'm not trying to be sarcastic or like, you know
Or oh, I'm I forgive this though. It's like I'm Jesus or something. I'm not
Probably closer to the devil than Jesus but
Who says the devil has to be a hateful a hateful being right
So I'm not saying whoo
What does it mean what does it mean if I you know, whatever I'm just saying I don't hold I don't hate
but I'm not like trying to fight with anybody
Really not pure like
Apologize it, but you know I know like the thing is I've been trying to make changes in a lot like a lot of ways
And I thought I have been in a lot of ways and it's like things keep getting brought up
Things that I've tried to change or have changed
like
And it's like, okay. Well, let's get
Right, I make I made mistakes. I started streaming live streaming not live. Oh, sorry live streaming maybe a year ago
But I started doing the panels
Probably eight months ago. So yeah, let's say like a nice amount of time
But it's not that long, you know people them people been in it for years and stuff like that. Okay, okay
It's okay. You can call me fans. I don't care. I don't care. And those are cute
I think there's a cute. Okay, I know I might I'm a misunderstanding. Hey, Nancy. Hold on. I got you Nancy
Yeah, okay, I just wanted to
Okay, here's more of this coffee. This is really good at the vanilla. Guys, on a McDonald's app,
you can get like every like 15 minutes or whatever they update it, then you can get like a new
thing off the app. But this is like for coffee, they charge $4 regularly for this coffee at McDonald's.
It's like 75% off and you can get several a day.
So I can get like, oh my God,
I can go like get like three of these a day or something
or four of these a day for like $4 instead of like $20, right?
Okay, I don't hate you either thing that is.
Okay, well, you're not blocked in the chat.
No, if you notice, but it's okay.
You know and in the future, I'm not just gonna like ban people if people ask me to ban them. I'll
Say to the person
Well, you can
You can block them
You don't have to see them because I noticed that even mods can block people in chat because I was able to block people in the chat
So I don't have to I don't have to see some comments if I don't want to see them and so
But only other moderators that I'm a mod in a chat. I can't I'm not gonna like not
Be able to see what a great like a regular chatter is saying right because I need to be able to protect the show
Or and so I need to be able to see that kind of stuff. Okay, so I apologize. I know I apologize and it was my mistake and I
sometimes I just like
And just like so willing to like oh, you know, please people or like one is like, you know, and I don't think about
stuff, you know, I don't know I
Sometimes I need to think about stuff a little bit and I understand so I think that's a better better way is to like, you know
Someone bothers you in the chat go ahead and block them
If someone bothers you on the panel and I'm gonna make try to make sure I really enforce the rules like I'll just like start
You know knocking people off the panel if they start with racists anything racist or doxing and any of that and mods
You know you have power to for that and if I miss things in chat, right?
so
Let's have like kind of like can we have like
Maybe it's like you think it's too late for a fresh start, but I love the concept of fresh starts. I love the concept of like
Let's
move forward in a different way or like, you know, in a better way, more thoughtful.
Um, because things do get confusing sometimes, it gets, it's a lot of people.
Hold on one sec, yeah, yeah, you can block me, you can block me.
Um, he man, yeah, I just want to make sure he hasn't, nobody panicked, like, you know,
But
Anyway, um, yeah, I just and I don't like and I know some people are you know not not anybody
I've seen here, but I know some people might try to play games with like the
You know with
In my favor or something like that with the rhythm with the I'm just saying I
Don't know. I just want
be fair and not be unfair to anybody I want to be fair to everybody if I
haven't been I'm sorry and I'll it's okay I showed my character okay that's fine
well I'm showing my character now too because you know I'm a lot more than
just five seconds of a decision I'm like a lot more than that that's not my
character my character is not
Anything hateful anybody anything hateful or anything
But finally you can judge for yourself that
Whatever people think of me. I can't control people thinking me. I can just control what I do and so
All I'm trying to be very not trying to be I am
feeling
Very calm
It's it's it's hard. I had the worst headache today like the worst headache and it's like the headaches
I really are the worst for me. It's like
I think I might know I can't think the call I know
Hey
Hi Alexandra, I see your thank you for stopping by and saying hi okay
yeah okay yeah not only I'm guys like really I have I'll have anybody on the panel except for
like foreign bombers and like that's really a foreign bombers or you know unless people like
people really haven't followed the rules I try and you know I guys I will I will forgive I will
So, for whatever, guys, also, not only on the show and stuff,
because I know it can be hard to like get a one-on-one,
if you want to get a one-on-one, be on the show.
But, you know, there's other ways to reach out to me.
I think I have my, you know, an email,
email and my page.
if you want to like, you know, people, I'm on a Discord, I'm on TikTok and different things,
and also the message boards, there's a message board in the member section,
there's also the regular message board. I think everyone's welcome. I don't know if
everyone can post on it, I'm not sure how that works. I haven't seen anybody post on it yet.
Hello, KZ. But, you know, it's always like if there's a real problem,
We can talk about it, but it's hard to talk with an audience sometimes about some things
because everyone's going to put opinions, and when there's too many people on the panel,
I get really overwhelmed.
I get that I'm sensitive to energy.
I had a really bad headache, not just from people yelling at me, but just from me yelling.
I don't like to yell, and it's like, wow, I don't think I've gotten like that.
I don't think I've screamed like that. My voice is kind of bad today. My voice is I lost a little bit of my voice
That's not me I'm not aggressive. I don't I'm not really into you know, I do like
Sometimes, you know, get involved in the drama and stuff like that. I think it's entertaining for some people and so something I
Just like a more I just like a good nature
Good nature kind of thing, right
Yeah, and I know Jamie and it's like I know and some people say well
I've given you so many chances low look to me, right? And it's like I know
Maybe I maybe I deserve a second chance. Maybe I don't deserve like a 20th chance or whatever, but
Um, you know, I can always try to do better. I can always try to improve.
Yeah.
Hello, right? Hi.
I think, um, somebody wants to link in the church.
Okay, I think I know I don't know how to do it though. I probably should learn how to do it
I can I can pin it. I'll pin it right now
There you go, I don't think I don't think mods can pin links, but
Yeah, copy pasted or something yeah, so I did it's pinned and
Yeah, anybody's welcome up
Like I said, I'm not going to do, I mean, I'll do if somebody would like to ever buy
the banner space for a few hours, I'll have that, but it's like I'll keep the panel open
for everybody and not say, oh, I'm going to charge open panels or whatever, just because
it just gives the wrong vibe, I think.
Hello.
Hi, Dane.
Hi.
Hi, sorry, you're having a pretty rough time, aren't you? Oh
I'm doing better than I was earlier today, but yeah, it's so it's so rough and it's like but
I have optimism. I have optimism that
It will get better. It will get better
All I can do is try try my best to fix things carry on
I'm not telling you to stop or anything like that, and I'll probably still watch it from time to time, but
You know unless this actually gets resolved. I can't be a part of it
Right. Well, we can read how do we resolve it? How do we fix it?
What do you think? I?
mean I
Don't expect you to come right and right out and say that no
You didn't you weren't involved in it because you haven't seen the the evidence yourself either
But I do expect you to say that what you should have done at that moment
Even if that was your best friend coming to you is going
Okay, show me the proof. I'll ban them immediately
That's all I would have been fine with that
Because as soon as she showed you the proof I would been okay. She got me
Because there is no proof
It was unfair to you and you know, and if she comes and everything
I'd like her to tell her side of the story too because I don't have
Maybe access to that conflict that part of the conversation now because you know
So, you know, that was the dumb on my part because then I can't you know
I
You don't you don't I I know what you're saying, but I'm specifically talking about be this chat where this all happened
She's accusing me of doxing her in beda's chat
But I did get a message from her, you know, and she definitely
Cleared it. She said that she doesn't think that you did that thing. She really
Yeah, and she thinks that you you might have encouraged it, which I don't think that's really on
the same thing, but you know what I mean, so
What a wonderful day this is.
So it turns out that I was right all along
and she is a worthless liar.
So I'm glad she came to me.
I'm glad she approached me right.
That's all I'm gonna say about that matter.
There's misunderstandings, there's misunderstandings,
and there's misunderstandings.
There is on the first one, but when the person being accused
goes in and confronts and says,
hey, wait a sec, I deny it, I did not do this.
So you got to show proof.
and they continue with the same accusation.
It's malicious after that.
I understood where you were coming from, you know,
before I started the panel and, you know,
kind of we talked behind, before I started going live.
And it really made me sad because I know you're like a man
that's fighting for your, you know, name
because you don't, you're not, you don't want to.
As you get older you realize that there's a lot less things that you really care about and things like integrity matter a lot more.
Yeah, peer integrity, that's what I noticed and I know that you were fighting for that, so I don't believe that you have that kind of a character at all.
I don't, I can be mean.
but I'm not like, I'm not dirty.
I could have just started talking about it.
I didn't even want to bring it up
until maybe she came in the chat,
but Psyche, you came in there
and started accusing things of that again.
So that's when I had to, you know,
actually bring it on.
All I said was what she said to me
and then my reaction to that,
because it's like she seemed upset
and it's like instantly I was like,
oh, here she's being picked on.
And it's like,
I just, like, I just, like, sugar watered her head.
Steve, even right there, Scythe, that's another thing that she lied to you, right to your
face about.
She said that I'm, that I was harassing her in your chat that day.
But if you actually were to look back at that chat, you would see that she came at me.
I wasn't seeing a damn thing about her.
She came at me, so then I responded, and then she went running up to the panel.
To tell you about it. So she's even lying about that. She lied to you about two things at the same time
Yeah, and someone is asking for a summary of the issue. I'll just say like, you know
Somebody said oh, you know thing that is
It is uh harassing me in the chat and listen first said she first said I
Doxed her then I confronted her and she started backtracking saying well no he's he was involved
He was cutting and pasting it and I said no wasn't even doing that you got a show proof of that too
And I don't know what happened since then now apparently she's done. She's taken it back completely so
Well, I mean I messaged her and I was like because I think she was sleeping, you know, yes
I was like we need to talk, you know, and
Basically told her I don't think think did that to you, you know, and she was like I
She said I have the message but she says something like she doesn't think it's you but she thinks that
Is a couple other people? I'm not gonna mention their name, but she thinks that you encouraged it, but that's like
right psych
Listen to what Beeta's saying right there, what Spunky apparently said, okay?
And remember the confidence that she had when she was telling you yesterday.
Remember that.
And remember the glee you had when you blocked me.
And then ask me again if I'm okay with all this.
It was disappointment, but it was like, she basically said.
I'm like, I'm done with you unless you do it.
I don't know.
I was like, yeah, I kind of felt a little bit pressured
and maybe I made the wrong decision.
I apologize.
I made a mistake.
I can't say much more than that.
All I can do is apologize and sincerely.
And seriously, give Spunky some side-eye, man.
She does not deserve this trust that you're giving her.
Well, I mean.
This should be a lesson for you of her character, okay?
You take this as a lesson. This is this is so I
Dad a point that you store away for next time something happens you you think back to this goal will wait a sec
I remember she was dishonest about this
That's gonna go for for everybody that like I said, I'm not just gonna lock me because someone tells me fine
Fine
I'll say they can block
Dad points of me being dishonest to you as well and you remember those but I don't think you're gonna find any
Think I think she might have been confused because there's a lot going on and like you know when you are drinking on the panels
Like I am I could mix things up, too, but you say that
Listen listen
Wait, wait, I understand that for the first time. I understand that
But when she's being corrected a few times and then she goes out of her way to actually repeat it again
It's malicious at that point. I'm sorry. It's not a mistake
I just think maybe, Nike, you shouldn't be so quick to take, you know, everything and
just be, you know what I mean, maybe look for proof and listen to other side of the
story as well, because it can be hurtful to people that are here and support you and
really, they really like you.
You know what I mean?
And like, yeah, if somebody accused me of that, I would be pissed too, because it's like
a big blame.
Here I just doctor information. That's not something that somebody wants to be accused of here at all
Right. And really, where do I have to lose here? If I did do it? Why wouldn't I just say yeah, okay, so I
I'm just used to like, you know, so many so many trolls in the chat that kind of do
But I missed and it's like sometimes I miss some people get mad and so it's like, you know, she
I just I get confused too and I'm gonna take things slower and I'm gonna stop
I know but you've got this you've got this habit you've got this track record now that I've observed where you you kind of
Kick the people who are actually supporting you who are actually caring about you and trying to
Trying to to be a benefit to you to make your show better
Either you me think, you know, I was trying to tell you she's being racist as fuck and she's gonna, you know
People like my mods and just you know, and you were just like no
I you know just dismissed it and then I came on your panel to talk to you about it
And you were like well, I mean you me's been nothing but nice to me. It's like well psyche
Do you trust me like I'm telling you, you know
Well, I watched back again like you know that some of it has been clipped like when I was like
I could have started my life so I miss what she said in that chat
So when I started I had started my life, and I was like eating dinner and like and then
You came in and were saying that, and I thought you meant-
He literally told Bronzeberg that I wouldn't talk to you face-to-face because you're black.
Listen, yes. I didn't see that. I didn't see that, and I was looking at my head.
It's like, my word may not mean anything, but I definitely witnessed it. I saw it myself. I mentioned it.
I saw it, because now I've seen back the clip where it's like I saw with what was shared.
She was clear, pointing out.
His black skin like that meant anything like that mattered
And then she changed it and she's like I meant I was talking about black RG
And then she was like, you know just constantly just but I was like trying to explain it to you and you're like well
No, you know this and that I'm like, okay. I don't know
I already already told you she's deleting stuff in the chat like anybody saying anything about her and I wasn't even saying anything about her
But I'm observing her
Removes like comments and she's calling everybody else sensitive, you know
So
Apocrates that you've got to pay attention to because you're gonna you know, there's people out there that are gonna get hurt like you know
I'm not even going all out and saying she is full blown racist
But what she did there and beat his chat was definitely racist or your chat wherever it was whoever's it was
It's like pissed off. This is it
I was trying to say that and I even told you psyche just you know
Hang in there like it'll be fixed eventually whether it's with clumsy or whatever, you know, I'm trying my best, but you know, it's a
Sometimes you got to take accountability too and you guys were screaming at each other. It was a lot
I I don't know. I hope that I hope thing you can you know talk to spunky and maybe she can clear it
But I'm pretty sure that she kind of did I'm you know
Like her and I don't trust her and I still think she's a conniving liar, but I'll talk to her
Yeah
But I apologize if I didn't do a good job of trying to fix this, you know
The only thing I was asking you for was to hang on to that recording because that is the only thing that proves my innocence. I
didn't want
Vanishing and then I got nothing
That's the only reason you're involved the only reason
Yeah, it's it's fine. You're fine. I mean I heard it from her and she just definitely saying you were not like
The one who did it she doesn't think you're the one that did it
She thinks you anti like antagonizing. I don't know like you might have said some rude things to her
So she might have been like oh this person really is out there to get me, but I said she's discussing
I said because you you put a big glow on for her and I said stop
Stop simping beta. She's disgusting. That's what I said. Yeah, and I do think that I think she's disgusting
Hold on so Ziggy is backstage. I don't know the right time
Jamie I'm not I'm not pissed at you or anything like that. Well, all I said was all I meant about the character thing was I
Already saw it. You can't take that back, but I'm not mad at you or anything
The year now diggy. Yeah. Yeah, that's me
You know my voice come on. I'm not gonna fucking fuck you up
I just need to hear your voice. I just need to hear your voice.
Yeah, what's up, Peter? How are you doing?
Hi, good. How are you?
Well, I just got to watch the trip kick video on how you were beaten up a psyche.
I was beating up psyche?
Yeah, and the trip kick video, yeah. I thought that was kind of rude.
Flump?
Would you do it?
The second time I've done it live, and it's like he comes there and not really clear about
what's going on and starts going out at people in my chat and wants me to get me involved.
So I mean, this is an example.
I think it's like a back and forth with you two, both of you.
Like he's wanting to do something, you're wanting to do another thing, and then fucking
You know going at it that way. I was doing my thing. I was just doing my life, you know and
running my show
There are some issues that needed to be discussed
But they weren't even brought up until a psyche came in there and kind of brought it up and you know example right there is
So he was actually being upfront and personal about it. That's good. I think that's cool
Yeah. I mean, I was too. So I'm not going on psyche. I would say like I'm here right now in that way you hate about men whenever they're not upfront and personal and like, I don't know why you're saying like, I hate men or anything about men because I was actually defending on a lot of people are defense like you all the time. So I don't know.
Insight is defenceless. Like, I mean, that's why I tried not to chime in. I
I'm sure it's overwhelming when you've got a panel full of people
that you perceive are all against you and you're being yelled at.
Like, I totally understand.
Fuck yeah, dude. Fuck yeah.
Yeah, just got an envelope.
Like, when I used to join your panel,
and Alexander NYPD would be saying the worst, the worst.
Whenever you said that, like, he just wants the money.
I didn't really quite.
Understand what you meant
Um
Money he wants like he wants good people is what he wants
So I didn't understand that on the trip kick thing whenever you were like
Oh, he wants his money
Biggie when you're sitting there and other people's channel, and you guys are saying most horrible thing about psyche, which I would never ever say, you know
Last time about
So be the triptych video was basically it was like it was like what happened in your chat
Well, when Yumi said that about...
Yeah, the Yumi thing, right? Yes.
And what did I tell you about Yumi? I keep telling you, at least for a couple weeks,
she's walking around in your fucking chat, you come in my chat, and you start defending her,
and you're going at a guy that's clearly being like, I'm telling you,
she's being racist to the fucking guy, and you're like...
Which is you, right, which is you making, you know, you're taking off for a psyche at that point.
if you go later into the fucking trip kick clip,
which by the way, I used to be a clipper.
I just, I didn't want to do it anymore.
It's, that's some hard shit.
That's some pay attention shit.
Yeah.
And then later, fucking, you're like, fucking,
all he wants to do it for is fucking for the goddamn,
Mm-hmm. Yeah. Yeah. Thank you. Look at the channel and you like you you let psyche I let psyche on my panel and I come over
I'm like, yeah, so he doesn't give two thoughts because I was there from the beginning
I will not just saying other people are in there, too
But then you're gonna have somebody like you me fucking be like making decisions for you
I'm not making decisions for you, but have a little bit of fucking respect for me. Definitely. Mm-hmm. You don't have respect for
though is obviously. How do you know? I mean it was right there in the trip kick fucking clip.
I think that there was, I think you know what psyche does? Do you know everything that psyche
does too? What does he do? Do you know everything that psyche does?
He's been really cool to me. I mean you you've been okay. He's really cool to you then as a person
Why wouldn't you not like fucking tell you or fucking friends? Hey, this guy is cool to me like stop calling
So don't be a fucking two-faced
In all my observations, I've never seen Ziggy, badmouth, psyche, anywhere else. I've not seen them.
Yeah, but sitting on top of it, I'm letting other people do it.
I'm just saying, he's not in contact with that stuff.
And you're supposed to be, you know, able to talk before me, but I'm giving my observation.
Well, I'm giving my observation, but I really wanted to know how Ziggy felt about it because
I know he discussed that. He definitely said that. You've heard of him. Yeah.
Yeah
No clue what the fuck you're talking about I
What do you mean? I have no clue there. It's right there on trip kick. I just told you right let's go
Trip kick is a freaking clipper and a lot of wine. So he is
Documented
Okay, so don't think for a second that I'm like, oh my god, Tripp kicked it.
Anything.
What are we doing?
I want, I want to say this.
I'm with you're not there.
I'm not defending myself. I was actually here to try to resolve something between thing and psyche, but you're here to just like, you know
I hate saying the word shut up. I hate that but I have had my woman Jan and
I knew you how long have I known you Bita? It's been a while
I've known you way before psyche, right?
Right and then
No, and then no, no, no, and then this woman fucking I introduced my woman to her
Because it's important and she don't like you anymore
She's gonna be like, oh, I don't like you because you're late
That loud high-pitched shit right there is that you've got I bet you've gotten your ass beat before I'm sure
Anyway
Actually the other way around
Would you like to ask me my point is is that she goes she goes behind my back and
She goes and types to my woman
in a video
Hey, you need to take care of Zegi because yeah
I said calm down your foot. You know what? Do you okay?
She laughed
Zegi you came on my panel and I asked you
Because you are a girls club is what you are
Listen, let me tell you something. I will remind you, okay?
I don't want to fuck with you because you came on my panel
I did let you on and I asked you because people are saying that you're calling people the n-word and you don't like black people
And I asked you the other issue with that because I have a bunch of people one of my mods like
Yeah, so then I went ask you and you said yeah
Yeah, you're making up shit you little lady and psyche's awesome. Thank you
I can get Tracy up here and she'll definitely vouch for it. Yeah
This is why you were kicked out of Denny's too, Ms. Fearless, because you're fucking racist. Yeah
Yeah, let's have a girls club. Let's get a girl.
Whatever, I'd rather have a girls club than a racist club like yours.
Bring a dude up. Bring a dude up that knows me and you.
Don't know who Tracy is
You're just bringing up random fucking things
Psyche, what's up, dude? I do save all of my lives, you know that right?
Oh, yeah. OK. All right.
So I will fucking get at that clip where you literally said I don't like them.
I fear I don't fuck with black people.
I don't like them. This is why I say that orange.
I said, OK, then get the fuck out of here. Get real.
And I told your girlfriend, call me your fucking man. That's it.
No, you didn't you said please mama get with get get Ziggy. Oh off my back
Yeah, and I'm off my back like I need you I don't need fucking her help. I'll just say
Fucking I think it's weird though that you and I knew each other fucking way long ago, and then you turn to fucking
Well, I'm explaining to me that she's not racist.
She doesn't like interracial, like, mixing.
But you heard me say, like, I don't like Black people.
Come on, man.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You're telling Psyche that he's turning on you?
And I'm like, add it to the fucking web.
She turned on me, man, this woman right here.
Furned on me long ago when as soon as she found out Jen was that you're fucking racist
I did turn on you yep
You turn to my panel and she explained to me that her beliefs are not like your belief
She said that you know what this is not what I believe what I believe
No, we have no no
Password and you deleted it
Deleted what the comment? No, I didn't yeah, you know, I
Maybe she deleted I don't even know what you fuck you're talking about. I didn't delete it if I
Was gone oh my god, no, I did it
No video is still there
Look, it's not a fucking big deal. I left a fucking comment saying control fucking Ziggy. You're fucking annoying. Yeah, mama
Yeah, control. Why would I go?
Mama, I will stand on this. She's your mama. What?
That was weird I thought mama you don't even know her
I blank out for a sec.
Mama, why is Mama being said?
Yeah, yeah, she's saying control Ziggy, Mama.
That basically, at the end of the day.
Oh, I see, I see, okay.
Yeah!
Like what?
Oh my God, what a big thing, oh my God!
Yeah!
because you're trying to be manipulative and that's what you're doing
that's manipulative like it's clear it's fucking like it's so clear
i'm on the same side with you girl team listen you take my fucking thing you go
at fucking crystal crystal would get mad at me i didn't let you up when crystal was up there
you're the one who fucking started turning on me ziggy remember that man on top of it you come
in the chat and i let you up again i'm like ziggy this is what's going on
Certain people are telling me you just said this on Vinny's channel.
I know what you do, I know how you work.
Yes, on Ms. Fearless's channel, you were saying, you were calling people to N-word with a hard
R. You're a little crazy now.
They were very offended.
I asked you and you said, yep, I don't like black people.
I know what is happening.
And you fucking double down on it, and I was like, okay, then get the fuck out of here,
then.
He's fucking motives.
He's trying to do his thing, and you're...
Honestly to God
Well I can do this, like a psyche can make an excessive decision right now
Psyche do you want me to go forever?
Yes
Oh, because he's too nice. I'm gonna speak for him and say
She doesn't love you but she doesn't love you
It doesn't matter if you're upset in a relationship you don't even know the fucking shit that happened
She told me that I'm just saying
Tell me what she said
He wasn't letting bronze bird up. I tried a freaking joint and it was all because like you me you me you me
I'm like, you know what fuck that you're fucking like
No, and you were a little jealous, I'm sure I don't know I wasn't there
30 people they're watching and I
So do you people watching?
That's what she cares about, Psyche.
I'm going to be on this.
Listen, if there's already a big panel going on,
and if I don't like what's going on,
I'm not going to be like, I'm going to go right now
and do this, because Psyche was welcome there.
She finds you as a competitor.
That's what's going on.
Oh, wow, I'm really, really scared
that I'm competing with Psyche.
Well, that's offensive.
I'm not trying to compete with anybody.
See, she just did it.
She said, oh, wow, I'm really scared.
Like I do try if I'm not at the same time if I'm not at the same time
I'm trying to make sure to put her link in and say everyone go
Do your thing man
Let me ask you is she putting is she putting your Lincoln?
I was the first person to share psyche is fucking no. Are you still doing it?
Yeah, absolutely. I send people there all the time. I'm like you guys I'm gonna end this if I keep live. Let's go over there
That's okay
So is so there is Sykes though. I mean both of them promote others. I've seen it regularly. Okay. All right
Nothing me and psyche are fine like we literally
We felt you don't know anything about our friendship like you don't know you are
No, you don't. Oh, you don't know me at all. I just told you how you are
Because you said it
You did that to me. I know so if I had anything like god if I wanted psyche to get dragged
I would definitely not try to fix his relationships with people like clumsy last night. It was a
Ongoing thing they resolved it right. I was working on bronze bird. I was like trying my best
I was like even defending psyche. I was like psyche fight back
You know, say I got this going I got this going and they were fighting back. They were fighting back and forth
So I do defend my fucking friends
Time the bronze bird bird one will meet time. It's too
It's too heated right now
Well, psyche came up there and he was, you know, you know, I love what she's like, I'm innocent and I never do anything wrong, too.
I never said I was fucking innocent. I don't do anything wrong. But every time I go live, I'm not going to fucking take the blame because there's going to be somebody that's going to say something bad about psyche.
One person, one or two people called him a fucking scammer and grifter and he went on.
Yeah, why you listen to why you
listen to Ziggy Ziggy's a JTLG
Go ahead. I'm letting everybody up. I'm letting whoever wants to do open panel and I'm letting a discussion and it's like
Yeah, yeah, Sam man. You better listen. You better listen because Ziggy's a loser. Fuck Ziggy. Fuck JC.
What is a loser?
I don't like you. You're a weirdo, bro. You're a weirdo.
You even are a weirdo.
You love JC. You love JC MLD.
You love JT-Doc's kids.
What are you talking about?
Yeah, they Doc's kids.
You love that shit.
I don't know what they're talking about.
Get the fuck out of here.
Yeah, you do.
And JT-Doc's kids.
No, I don't.
JT-Doc's kids.
Oh, JT?
No, he doesn't.
Yes, he does.
Man, you're crazy.
No, he doesn't.
Everybody know.
Yep, salute.
Look, Ziggy.
Ziggy.
Everybody knows over here that JT-Doc's kids.
You try to say that's okay.
Hey, I don't know about that.
I don't know what you're saying.
I don't know about that.
I've never said that.
Go to his channel.
No, he's making me up.
He may have pictures of other people and all that,
but that's different than Doxing Kid.
I don't know.
I don't have a picture of a kid on your platform.
It's wild.
Hey, listen, man.
I hear you.
I hear you, Sammy.
I'm not saying you're incorrect.
I'm just saying.
I want to show somebody else, hold on, I want to show, hold on, I want to show somebody else kid on my platform on my community war, that's not fair.
You don't, you don't show nothing anyway.
But the point is, is that JT doesn't do that.
JT got all his community war.
Ziggy, Ziggy, are you listening stupid? It's on JT's community war. Go check your community war.
I don't know why you say the word stupid.
Go check your community war.
Go right now, hop off the panel and check his community, you all.
Dude, I know what you're talking about.
All right, then.
That's a job, dude.
Some of the other people, some of the other people in that group,
openly say that they've got doxing stuff on their community thing, but...
Jake, he does it too!
I'm just saying JT isn't one of the ones that has done it.
He does it, though.
OK, I'm just saying there are people
who have admitted that they do that.
I know.
You're talking to us, man.
JT Rain does it, too.
They do it.
What you think?
No, JT does it.
JT does, like, damn it.
I don't know why you lying.
JT don't just do gaming.
He wants to do gaming with two viewers, by the way.
But want to call people PDF-er-gillers.
Go look at his fucking views, man.
Nigga, nigga, two viewers.
I went over there, stupid.
No, stupid.
I went over there.
What do you call him?
Nigga, JT gleaches off psych.
He's trying to hone the psych in, nigga.
Fuck the game, too.
Fuck out of you.
Fuck all over the nigga.
Nigga.
Dude, some of his gaming chain is like 400 fucking views, man.
It's 400 views.
Go watch.
400 views.
Yeah, that's pretty impressive to game.
Yeah, because gaming is not the big deal.
It's like when you used to game, you got fucking like 200.
I still game.
Nobody cared about it.
Yeah, nobody cared about it.
I did.
I fucking came over and was fucking.
I don't know why you're calling me a weirdo you're a weirdo ass nigga. I don't know why
I just told you nigga. Go fuck. Go suck JT dick faggot
My fault my fault my fault my fault like maggot
If I say something the way I want to say it then I get kicked
You not mean nigga
Right exactly
Yeah, yeah
You're based in on the white
There would I be I'm sorry to interrupt y'all y'all cook. No. No, you're
Wondering what the fuck like ziki was like
There's sitting there talking about psyche for like three hours calling
You're such a good friend. You didn't even say once like hey this guy doesn't have fucking a
Like stop bragging on him. He tastes care of a fucking cat. JT. I wouldn't let anyone talk to thank you like that
That's for sure when they go
All they do is talk about that's all they do
Talking to 20, talking to four or five people
about Psyche and Vita and me.
Did you guys didn't watch that?
I don't talk about you.
I don't give a fuck about you.
You're not there when Psyche is hurt
and he's actually like his heart is broken
and he like, listen Psyche, just ignore it.
Like it's not true, so ignore it.
You're not there, right?
But you're there.
I don't know why they're fucking talking all this shit about me
But you're gonna fucking come at me for being honest with psyche or even venting on some of the shit that he's done
While JT and Gotti suck psyche dick on panel and it go live and talk shit about him
Well, that's what they do. I don't do that.
I'm just saying, man.
You're a dick writer, man.
Man, the fuck up.
Man, fuck you.
Well, get rid of him, bro.
Like, Ziggy.
Well, what's Ziggy on the panel anyway?
I wanted to do it.
I did it because I did one of the dreads.
Because I was taken up for fucking psyche.
Yeah, let's psyche talk.
What?
Go on.
With Ziggy.
So I was in, like, the Spunky's, you know, Spunky's chat,
like, after everything had ended and then I, like, you know,
I don't know if you were there or you were just in the after the after show at that
But they were pretty brutal with I think he wasn't there. I saw it too psych this first time
I'm telling you but I saw it too. You are not lying in what you what you said
I was probably drunk man and was not there
Yeah, so he was he wasn't when I when I cut when I taught them like you know when they didn't know I was there
Whatever they knew I was watching the live after cuz I you know, I admit
You know, I said on my show like psyched. They don't give a fuck about you my nigga. Just move on
That's what I'm trying to tell psyche these motherfuckers don't give a fuck about you. You know what this guy up here
What are you talking about? Was he there Erby? Sorry man. Okay. If he was I I forget I'm not
That was that was not Erby. I think you're talking about the show after big I'm talking about
Sam and won't shut the fuck up
Ziggy, you be talking shit to a bus, like, nigga.
There's people, there's people I've noticed in that chat that did not work out, really addressing me.
I don't think Ziggy really said anything specific about it.
I never saw Ziggy say anything, okay?
Um, and I didn't see anything.
Same here, Brian. I don't see anything.
I didn't see, you know, it was Gotti and B.J.T. and then Rain and Vicky were all talking,
like, you know, saying, oh, CB, CB you're talking about, yeah, CB, yeah, and, and then
also I kind of recognized Justine's voice because some, but some woman called it instead
Oh, oh, you have facial deterioration because that's from HIV medication, and since then...
From Vicky. From Vicky too. Vicky's a scum. Vicky's a scumbag. Vicky's a scumbag.
I
Okay, she's a mouth for you Vicky's a scumbag
Vicky is ugly as fuck you see how
She's ugly Vicky no teeth no nothing y'all talk about me Vicky got no teeth at all I think she's saying I'd seen her
I was harassing her
Graham cracker
But people believe things like you know, so she's she keeps repeating in chat or maybe her or I don't know
There's different names, but it's like he's saying oh
Sticky was sexually harassing Vicky in the chat and so I shared all the chat and all the you know the stuff
Hold on. I'm gonna re-summer up one second. Let's make sure I'm fun. Fuck Vicky. Fuck
Fuck yeah, that's fucked up man. Oh, you don't like
Can I talk to you for just two seconds? Can everybody just give me two minutes, please?
Like yeah, I just want to say that this party was you know me and you kind of got into it
I kind of snap to and I want to own my own accountability
I love you to death psyche, and I just get frustrated
Sometimes and I had a lot going on. I had a really big case which we did really good in court today
So that might have been why I was a little bit extra edgy
but
Just want to say that you know, I love you to death and you know, I'm not going anywhere, and I'm not gonna not support you
Let me talk please
And so I felt like sins, you know I'm saying I cussed you out in front of everybody
I should come up and also apologize
This is how that works man whenever you're friends you
I got a question for Ziggy now that we did that Ziggy, so you're racist. Yes
No, I'm not but we already talked about this in in a relationship. I choose we've already done this summer
Yeah, well, I don't have a
Yeah, and I don't have a problem with that. We've talked about that because there's
Do you use the heart do you use the N word with the hard R just yeah, yes, yes, yes, yes, he does
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes
I got clips of you
I'm not cooking I'm asking you this because I actually have black children. I have a black husband
So I don't want to you know, I mean if you're if you're using that word. That's really hurtful towards me and my family
So that's why I'm asking
So she asking you did you say it because I got clips that could show that you say it
What I just think that's a stupid part of you. Oh
Don't know I'm not dude. I am not mating with a fucking black woman
Me and my husband me but my husband's on there and just like I told you I know plenty of latinas
I say what I think as I know people that are black this day with black. There's nothing wrong with that
I don't have an issue
But that's not what I'm talking about. I'm just asking you. Do you go around throwing this term?
Because again, I have black children, so like I'm gonna be cool with somebody
I don't want somebody that's gonna be using that kind of that word
With with my with my best friends that are around me and they all black
So I don't I don't I don't say nothing like that man, but you do say the hard are
But you got best friends that are black.
Shout out to you, Ziggy.
You look.
All right.
Well, I was just asking my question.
I just mainly came up for Psyche.
Psyche, I love you, and I'm proud of you.
I love you.
And I'm OK, too.
You do say the hard R, nigga.
I've got clips of you saying it, stupid.
You got it.
You're thinking of Q.
I'm thinking about you, Ziggy.
You used to argue with Amber a lot.
You used to say the hard R for no reason.
i don't know what you're white people say with everyone i'm not gonna tell anybody what they
can say i just like was fucking i think it's thinking about hold on one second i literally
addressed you on my panel about this ziggie when you joined my panel the first thing i said to you
is that did you just come off of somebody else's panel and you said the fucking hard part you're
like yeah i'm like are you racist and you're like yes i don't like black people yes i got the
Nah, I don't joke around with the horror, I don't joke around with the horror.
I'm not gonna sit here and just fucking like, you know, say it's not the fucking truth.
He definitely said it.
And then his girlfriend came up and cleared it, and she's like,
I don't have an issue with black people, I just don't like...
I wanna know something.
What is our...
I'm out of here. Yeah, I just try to give an excuse to Ziggy
Apologize to each other. Okay, and I'm pretty much
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
i'm not here to confront him i'm gonna suggest to psyche i came up here actually clear something for
seeing and that was it pretty much what i like that was what i would say that i don't i don't
i don't have a problem with anything beatus that i am absolutely fine with beat up beat and i
worked you know talked about you know this stuff and it's like so whatever i saw on trip kick it
It was the same fucking night, like, you and me were, like, defending her shit.
She's, like, freaking calling Bonsberg shit, and I'm, like...
I'm bitching over him and him again.
He's got it now, causing, uh, causing shit, too.
She's terrible, man.
The infamous...
The image is weird as fuck.
She's in, like, the Middle East, man.
The infamous...
Um, GL...
Fuck, where is she at?
She's weird, right?
She's Toy Girl Silvers.
Are you there infamous? Yes. Hello. Hi
You just gave me a rent you just
You might be in a different name. Are you what's your name on the chef? Oh?
Fucking miss you buddy. What the fuck have you been? I have a German lady
Fucking miss the hell out of you. What have you done?
listening to your racist ass.
I'm not racist, you're my asshole.
No, no, I've known Ziggy for a while now.
I don't think Ziggy is like racist racist,
but you know, he comes from IP2 and IP2 is like.
There's clumsy.
They go around, that's like kitchen, that's like kitchen.
Can I say something real quick?
Real quick and I'll jump off.
Samman defends people that says the heart ER word. He defends people that says the heart ER word
So don't don't don't let that little boy get in y'all's head man
His homeboys fucking say the heart ER word his boy
Yo, have I ever fucking said the part R to you
Don't know but everyone says it bro. Everyone on this panel's probably said it
So as soon as he came, I've already been told like, look, Ziggy is saying the shit.
I don't really, I don't feel comfortable with being like in the chat with him, this and that.
So I asked him, I was like, Ziggy, are you, you know, did you say that word?
He said, yeah, but did you say, but are you racist?
You're not like black people. He said, no, I don't like black people. I don't.
He's like, I fuck with them, but I don't like blacks.
That's what he said, as I think get the fuck out of here though, and I take them.
You little manipulating bitch, dude, that's fucked up.
Well, I just think it's a secret of how they work.
I get everybody around here says it, and I just think it's them.
I have like heard like people like you and Aldi and it's like I think like a lot of people are cool with them and
I wouldn't do I said that I wouldn't fucking have sex and have kids with a black woman
That's what I said and she's turning things around
Little bitch
She calls you worse names
I never said that, I don't know, they're saying it.
The worst thing I've ever said to you is like literally
what I felt at the moment.
It's never been anything draugatory.
I've never been like, you know,
Ew, you're disgusting. You're like got AIDS. Like I hope that like, you know, you got shut under your fucking nails.
You don't take care of your cat. No, I don't do any of that. I'm very honest with them. There's issues that come up.
People come on my panel. They're like, Hey, I'm mad at him for this reason. I feel this and this and that. And I try to resolve it.
Look, it's clumsy. One of them didn't like each other till last night. They're fine.
No, no, come on. Let's let's just I want to talk keep talking civil
I want to work things out some things out on you know in this Congress
I wanted to be working you know working something with out with somebody that doesn't work something out with you
That's what's nice. Yes, you just because beat and I have
Behind the scenes we're talking in a week. You'll be right back here
Promise, you know, it's like brothers and sisters fight too, and I think that's what kind of like we're kind of like that closely
Oh, you know, yeah, that's what I was gonna say cuz me and psyche also fight a lot, but we always make up
So I mean if people hang on our arguments and think we're gonna stop talking they're crazy cuz we're not
exactly exactly it's the enemy
I get emotional sometimes things get heated sometimes
sometimes I'm drunk and you know last night
I did not see my sleep bite video
but
But to be fair and all let's be let's be fair though the person's in here trying to fucking
Drag down fucking Ziggy, which sad man. He protects people that say the heart of artwork. Come on now
Exactly
They are there is there is there is all of them
Color he's of color
Is he black?
Charminley.
Is he
Say it too. Let's be honest. They say it. It's like
With the a not with the hearty
I mean, they're the only ones that have the right to say it really to be
But but give give German ladies some room. I mean, you know
No, I would never use that word. I think the word is disgusting in my opinion. However
If people grew up in certain grew up in certain places and certain areas or something
You've got to keep your blood from normal normal language. It shouldn't be but the reality is you know
Well
You can put the sentiment a little less racist that that's I think that's the problem
I think yeah, maybe yeah, and I'll say to German lady. It's me. It's me
You know, we'll show this in pagan
Right, yo, where do we talk master about psych and he's up here now. I just love the moonwalking over
They always come back
I don't want your man. I don't want your man
i don't want your man bro why did everybody like everybody copied like same
man like the pop-up thing man that's bro he's jealous bro i've never met a jealous man that
doesn't want me to have fucking friends with people online bro like come on get get a reality
chick sad man for the pop-up thing the i'm cooking pop-up like that shit to me is get a reality
But you're really my friend online, right clumsy, but yeah, but you know what?
I'm just as guilty, bro. I'm
I got black people in my family though homie, but do I sit there need a boy?
Let me do that. No, no. Me too. My brother is black. I have a
Black half brother. I want to say this. I want to say this like for a month
I'm not gonna be fucking rude or anything anything that's already done
Then I fucking love black people man. Look at clumsy man. He's been nothing, but true, dude
Hold on, I know but Sam and Sam
Asshole, well, no, no, you gotta let me finish you gotta let me finish before you laugh
But like for me and that is my preference is all I said
is that I would never, you know, be with another of the opposite.
That was all.
And then he...
And you talked about that, and just like I told you, there's nothing wrong with saying that.
Right. Yeah, I remember that conversation
Summer that was the first time I ever came up on your panel and I was and I say what I need to say and
I knew I was getting thrown off. Well, guess what you didn't throw me off. You were like, no, I respect it
That was important
Only day black people like they know it's their only day left
You know what I mean? There's nothing that I don't have an issue with and I understand why people do I personally obviously am not
I am an interracial marriage and I love my husband. I'm black children. I'm mixed children
Yeah
Look look you guys
Like if if rain and I hung out with her husband or whatever and there's there's her kids
I'd play with them. It's already
Yeah, it's just not my thing to reproduce
like I can't I'm not that's not what you can't just say you're not sexually
attracted to to them I mean yet that's that's perfectly fine
you can't help what you're sexually attracted to it's not
I'm gonna I'm gonna hop off I'll catch you later I hope you know you have a good life
well the lady was really good hearing your voice again I love your voice
you catch you later summer see you guys later
And it was
I'm a weirdo cuz I like while German ladies voice you're weird. Yeah
Now I didn't try to be like a fucking a thorn in someone's ass and shit
But I'm just saying don't be a hypocrite towards other people when other people do it though
But this is why my bad if I fucked up your panel, but a salute to everyone
Hey, you have a good day
On a scale from one to ten how much were you aroused when you saw clumsy shirtless
Cl- Oh, Clumsy Shirtless?
Um, let me see.
Which way?
German Dolls.
You know, he's a- I mean, he's a good- I remember the first time I saw him on Joker's
show, I was like, oh, who's this super- you know, I like Latino guys, uh, you know, then
work out and then, you know.
We kind of didn't get along all the time, but now we kind of like, you know, buried the hatchet over the hatchet.
I don't know. Buried the hatchet.
Yeah. Buried the hatchet last night.
Like, you don't know that's a word.
I know. I know it for years.
Like, I'm really, this is like one of the rare times I go on panels like this.
I stay in Miley most of the time.
But I know these people for like, since like 2022, as clumsy, you know, I know that.
I think it's, I think it's false.
Like I'm no new since what like 2019 I think
No, I'm pretty sure 22
You sure yeah, I first saw you in embers chat
Ember
Oh, not and oh not impressed, but ember HHH HHH HHH
Oh amber amber. Yeah, okay
Well, that was okay. That was right after the Audi 1k thing
Yeah, yeah, that's no no no when when LD LD used to run panels when
Fucking what's his name?
John Smith was still alive
She knows about John Smith
I'm relatively new to the you know the you know
I've been doing the open panel since January and so I'm pretty you know
I've met a lot of these a lot of the people like you know pretty new
relatively
but uh
You know I'm trying to trying to catch up a little bit. I'd like to
Get to know people better and yeah, I think I think dude if I may I think that the fucking dude and literally I quit trolling
I mean ask ask German lady. I don't troll much
Yeah, I haven't really done much
Just when you're drunk those Iggy
But the dude beside you I think you need to start listening more to him man. He seems like a more
Cold dude me like yeah
Like I feel like you're like telling the truth about stuff and you know like yeah, what about this?
You know, and I think that's what friends need you know
Yeah, I like yeah, I like genuine and it's like and I'm you know, it makes me feel even worse just for like, you know
Pre-judging or jumping to conclusion and it's like, you know
I learned lessons, I do learn a lot on this, I do learn a lot, especially because I'm a little bit socially awkward, you know, I'm a little bit, I'm not really...
We all are, that's why we're on YouTube, we all are, don't worry about it.
Oh no, no, what? What do you mean? Dude, I've been on stage and stuff.
I went to like a really, my school, 6th through 12th grade had like 200 students, 6th through 12th grade, so like I had a very, very small like little shelter.
You were like a little talent show or something?
I did, I did like community theater, a few community theater stuff, and like I was into drama and things like that.
Dude, I don't even know where, what state are you in?
Help I'm in LA. Oh, you're in Cali fucking go to Texas man
And fucking you can sign up for that kill Tony you fucking show. That's can you do some well?
I was yeah, I could I could come up with some material and like perform and I could get I love that show man
Yeah, that's so cool. I could I couldn't me. I couldn't do that. I could never do that
I'm comfortable like actually like on this show. I'm comfortable like on like on a stage and able to like
But it's still like when it comes to like the social dynamics. I'm pretty awkward with it
Like, you know, I don't like I just like I'm empathic and stuff like that
But it gets very you're overwhelmed with like and I'm very sensitive to energies and stuff like that
I pick up on
Don't be sensitive
Well, I'm just like in the way that it's like I'm
You know, just like I'm I'm intuitive empathic. I feel I take on other people's emotions. Sometimes I'm very like oh god
All I do that to people only do that to people that are close to you man, but whenever you
Yeah, but you can't help it if it's something like that. Yeah
It's just it's just it's just like, you know, it's just like I'm a I'm a you know, kind of naturally
Yeah, you don't pick and choose, right? It's just how
I'm sensitive to energy, especially sensitive to negative energy.
I think you need to have the dude beside you to fucking be your manager.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Yeah, I do love uh, you know, I do love honest people and I do like the blunt people and you know blunt people and
That's my question. I think I think I think everybody here today is spoken their truth like you know
And it's my truly a totally dead. Yes. Yeah
That's why we had your little bitch left right well, you know, I don't think it's like I you know
I love me I don't
Yeah, I know. Yeah fucking. Oh, you weren't here. I
Don't want to put her down. I don't know later. You weren't here, but he doesn't she doesn't care about this guy at all
She does she does she really does and it's just like
You can get you most upset sometimes the people closest because we actually really do care about some people's a bit
I don't care about no, it's real simple psyche really cares about
life and then Bita she cares about numbers of views and fucking about
Thank you cares more about views and stuff like them be that is honestly
Marketing as well as a mark I have a marketing degree and it's like and so I look at you know
And so I look at the show both is like I like to have fun
But I put so much time into it, I do want to be monetized and stuff, you know, I've thought of different ways and sometimes I guess that way they don't quite work out and it's like a little hard for other people to do fun.
She's not really down for you dude, it's kind of weird.
I know it's like I think she does man. She does care about him. I
We talk about it and it's like I mean look at the trip kick video
They have a different kind of relationship, but there's definitely there's care for each other there
Relationship do you think that they'll be together at one point no not like that. No
Hi, rain. How are you? Hi, good.
How are you?
I was I was told like, you know, oh, you called rain the sea word.
I don't remember ever doing that.
If I did in some moment of anger, like, I don't I don't use that word.
I I get you were angry and I said the
I said what I said in JT's panel because of that.
Like, yeah, you're calling me the sea word and the B word.
I I.
I
That's not a word I use and so that is very out of character for me German lady. What do you think?
I cannot remember that, but I don't I don't I mean, I don't think I don't I don't like
Ladies now, it's like ladies
Apologize if I did that okay
Yeah, and I apologize for what I said at JT's to
I like oh remember Ziggy like well, I don't think you remember you're probably drunk
Goddy Goddy was talking about psyche's 30 fingernails and then I added you know, he probably has HIV under those fingernails
Shit like that, you know, but
It's just it's just a normal troll, you know like
I can't stay long excuse me. I didn't mean to interrupt you but
Uh, what's his name? Ziggy has been calling me a bitch like 3, 4, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3
You know, not my cup of tea or whatever you get so much. Yeah
Playback what they were saying every last night if you don't remember, okay, there was there was calling me griptor scammer
Anyone they would call me on your panel, you know, remember what Alex would call me uncle
Right
kicked way before me, guaranteed.
Well, see, I don't know.
You keep mouthing off, we'll find out.
All right, well, I can make it happen really easily.
Do you know what she said about you?
She said, crazy shit about you.
Oh, really?
Well, the craziest thing I ever said about him.
Because you said that he doesn't get enough views,
and I thought you were nuts.
When I'm live and he comes over there and like cause of the scene because of you meet chaps the fucking retard and then goes
Like you
Okay. Thank you. I will never come back because
I don't even know if you like it. I'm going to be honest.
Not good. Not good. Because you know, Biggie, Biggie, I bet you money. He'll always choose
me over you. You'll never be a modem here. You'll never, he will never trust you.
Yeah. But I'm sure that he's now bringing back how you're acting right now.
No, I mean be this by I just like I beat it's like I I'm just letting everyone talk
And I want to try to work things out, and it's like, you know, there's information
My work here and all I hear is beta beta bitch bitch bitch, okay
When people come on my panel
Because you're really quiet, but I always have to fucking defend you, right? Okay. All right
Okay, no, no, no, I will defend you.
That's her defense?
That's her defense, yeah.
I think I've sucked up pretty several times.
I was taking up for you, but yeah,
I remember she's on her own panel, she's like,
I can't.
That's fucking crazy.
Ziggy, Ziggy, Ziggy, if you do it one more time.
I'm gonna take you off the show.
Okay, please.
That's what she said.
Please do not call her that name.
You idiot.
Let's not make names.
Let's call people names.
Cause I want to talk to you about some stuff
and I want you on the panel to talk about some stuff.
And you're making-
Make it like literally obsessed with me.
Be that, be that, be that, be that.
He's trying to fucking like,
we keep trying to work things out,
but he's the one that's trying to break up our friendship.
Pay attention.
And a lot of people,
a lot of people are, I think,
because they're jealous of, you know, our relationship.
And it's like, I'm not gonna let it happen.
Yeah, I think he's a jealous asshole.
Yeah, obviously, Vita is not any of these bad names, right?
Vita is a wonderful person, she's awesome,
she has a beautiful heart, and we, Vita and I are cool, okay?
That's beautiful.
That's why Ziggy, Ziggy, Ziggy, Ziggy, Ziggy.
Don't, please don't, it's not funny, it's not funny, Ziggy.
Just like, just be respectful to everybody,
especially Vita, like, you know, don't,
because you've already called her out of her name,
and don't do that, don't do it again, please.
I do want to talk to you in the conversation, okay?
Well, you're not, just, just, just, just, just don't bring, just don't turn her up, okay?
Yeah, just don't bring me up, bitch.
All right, Ziggy, you're the bitch now.
She's calling me a bitch.
Yeah, you're a bitch.
There we go.
Don't bring me up anymore.
Thank you, Saiki.
Why is she doing that?
Why is she able to do that?
Shut the fuck up, bitch.
What the hell is this guy doing in the background?
He was riding the horse.
Having a girlfriend.
I had, I kind of looked at that at first two, like, what the hell's going on there?
But he was riding it.
I
This is having a garage sale or what the hell is going on
That's cool. I mean, yeah, it looks like a Mexican birthday party or something. I'm not I love the Mexican flag in the background
You got the the army
Or Texas I
Rico probably
I'm not sure I'm not sure I just don't I don't know I'm Canadian. I'd say it all looks the same to me
Okay, well the cardboard. He's doing some performance art and we can enjoy this while
Well, we all chat. Okay. Well, while beta goes back and comes down, right? I think we're making progress. I think we are making some progress.
We might. But, um, Psyche, I just wanted you to know where I was coming from. You know, I felt hurt. So, yeah, because JT and I, we've been nothing but nice to you and support your channel.
Um, even though we don't donate anything, you know, we donate our time and, you know, just panel time, you know.
that is one thing I do wanna say, JT has probably been the least offensive towards you and he's probably gotten the worst treatment.
I agree, I agree.
Yeah, he has.
In the same, same with me, I get treated that way from Bita and...
I had I mean I didn't have to like unmod him a couple times and he and I think some things were said that were
Okay, he was nice to you
Until you know, you were calling me those things right, but you know, but rain you were also whenever I would see a comment
From you would be something very negative. They usually towards me like and no, I was actually laughing at what somebody else said
Okay, maybe nothing nothing against you
Nothing against you
I don't know like what was going on I don't know if you were having like a paranoid episode or what happened, but yeah
psyche psyche
This is all I want to say psyche is that dude they have been nothing but cool to me man
Like for real
But I mean and I get upset sometimes and sometimes I mean like usually I hide people the next day
But it's like yeah, you're listening that no, did you see the did you see what she just did? I'm talking about
You stop already
Well, you know what? Like maybe everybody is you know, and it's like and I have I'm just I have to be my own
I'm not and rain isn't in the guy next to you isn't nobody's trying to pull
I mean guys I make mistakes. I tell you I tell you I've not I don't come from a bad place
I don't hate people if I didn't say say things it's because I've been triggered by something and you guys admit
Oh, we're trying to trigger him. We're trying to trigger him
You know and it seems like you know like like Gotti and G2 will poke at you, but that's it like no harm
They were saying oh look at the repair we triggered that paranoia tweaker like you know, yeah, that was all said in JT's JT's panel
That was all said it said it said in spunkies when I was there in spunkies like when nobody knew I was there
I just came she fell asleep and you were all chatting
and like laughing like I wasn't in spunkies actually you weren't maybe you weren't there but it's like
they or they all were okay it was gaudy it was um it was uh jt it was yeah because of the way you
were treating them us well i mean it's like like we've been supportive and then you throw us under
the bus like okay but you're coming from a very innocent place like oh i we were just all night
always nice and it's like no there was like a lot of
Negative stuff and it's like I mean I I know some of what you perceive as negative like you need to stop being so sensitive dude
For real like but I'm an impact and I'm psychic and it's like some of the comments were
We're vindictive. I mean you can tell that there was there was some animosity there. It's not just yeah, yes
Yes
Well, yeah, I mean like the way you were treating us wasn't fair, you know, and then we couldn't we couldn't come up because we were banned
Well, I mean and bannings here nevertheless. Yeah, he's like yeah
Everybody and then everybody last night and banned everybody three nights ago
I think by that point you were even on ban too, but it's and it's like even even after that God
He was like he I want to see I want to say one thing to psyche man
I really give a shit about your channel, you know fuck her. I don't care
And we're not out to destroy we're not out to destroy channels and shit, whatever, you know, like we're just here to have fun
Would you be interested in joining in the discord?
Yeah, I mean I can I can join the discord and it's like in fact I notice I'm a mod at CF for some reason
I don't know why like I don't know how that happened or win, but you are like I was in there
I was like I was a mod because I kept seeing you
You better get your ass in there
And you know, and I said, it wasn't like, even if you can go to the other night after the show, I was like, you know what, it was actually kind of a, I liked the music on the show, I was like, and some of what they were saying was funny, I liked some of the banter, but it was like, you know, even though it was very negative against me, it's like, really, and it's like, but I understand, misunderstandings and stuff like that.
You know, it's like so maybe it wasn't yeah, it was just a misunderstanding
To fucking join the fucking discord too, man, you you're a good dude me
Yeah, I
Don't do this court. Thanks. Oh, okay. Oh, you seem like a good upstanding guy, man
I'm on a discord. Well, I'm on this. I'm on this IP to discord and then today like we came up with
It's like there's crazy stuff like IP to such a homophobic and racist community for like
People are like, yeah, they're crazy
He's an IP to and then I know Saint and IP to I'm friends with Saint
We're gonna actually hang out like fucking one like I want to ask um thing why do you hate spunky so much?
Pretty good at judging character and I could tell right from the start that there's something off about this girl
And the more she kept going. I I'm like, yeah, yeah, I'm I'm I'm on it
I know I'm right and then she you know, do you know her personally or what?
Bunky are you talking about the one that I was like really fucking drunk? Yeah, just Justin Boyle's girlfriend
Oh shit, I don't know anything about her. I
Know you're talking about yeah, I don't I don't know her outside of
This YouTube stuff right here for over the last couple months
I'm just pretty good at judging character, and I can just pick up on things
Looking at her like
automatically you didn't like her no no no not not just by looking some of it is is body behavior
But most of it is is what they say is stuff like that. Yeah, I thought like it is spunky married
Spunky is spunky. No, she's with Justin Boyle
Yeah
Okay, so why are you guys even trying to hook up what we're not what were you trying to hook up with her?
What's going on?
No
No, are you saying raging demon passed away? Are you serious? I don't know. I'm seeing this in chat
I just don't even pass away. Yeah, that's right. Yeah, you did
I guess
I have no clue
I don't know. I don't want to
Saying that and I just don't know a legion demon is kind of gay though. I knew that
He's gonna be bad, but I know him
So repeat
Okay, what happened?
No, no, I'm talking to your neighbor you you talk to her and then no
We've never talked. Oh
You never talk. No, it's just why
You know seeing how she comments in chat the way she behaves
And then when she's going on panels just the stuff she said
Little things I pick up on and I I it just kind of kept growing that not there's something up with this girl
I like that like a cap growing and you're like, yeah, I get it and then at the end
So I have gt here. He wants to say something
You're asking psych, right? No, you don't even have to announce me
What the hell's going on I don't know at all
We were psyche. Oh, there you are
Like you what's the deal man?
everything
I'm absolutely fine. I'm trying to
Men some fences are trying to come to some understandings and at least if we can't I'll be friends, you know, I'd like to be
to be civil and things like that.
I'd like to smoke the peace pipe and, you know.
Well, we basically speed it a lot.
Is this your way of saying you're bad?
Because if so, that's fine.
Just I want to know.
You're not banned.
I haven't banned everything.
He said, you're bad.
My bad, it's like, I did, oh, god.
My bad, it's like, how about we all make mistakes
and sometimes there's misunderstanding.
I've made a reaction, I think, maybe.
Sometimes, maybe you, it's the best to change that I've been coming at me, okay?
I want to say, let's look, we can like start fresh, if, if uh, you know, I'm not gonna-
Look, like I say, I, I, look, I'm nice to people who are nice to me.
I was always nice to you, when you started treating me, my girl liked shit in me,
then that's when I was like, okay, fuck this.
But if you want to be cool, then we can be cool.
And that's something I can't go make going after a guy's girl is going to get the attention.
Well, I really feel like, I mean, I feel like there's things with things with both ways,
right?
And so we can like, you know, I'm willing to, you know, let bygones be bygones.
If you want to be cool, everything's cool.
That's as simple for me, like, I'm not.
Yeah, I just want to I just want to be civil
I want everyone to be to be able to come come on panel and I want to the only people
I really don't want on panel are just porn bombers or people that are like
And and not I mean like come on be da you don't
Where she puts you down what do you mean?
I'm going to walk away. I'm going to walk away. I'm going to walk away.
I'm going to walk away. I'm going to walk away.
You will shoot what are we? I can hear by your voice. You will tumble away. Oh
Shit, is that your is that German lady?
I love her show. What's up German lady?
German lady you need any of your number and who's that thing in the years
Thing that is so the whole I wanted to ask about the whole spunky thing
So you're the guy that like are you the guy that Doc spunky? No, no, you're not here. You're not him
That's so weird she's like she's like yeah, she's like yeah, he's that guy
So unless there's proof, we need to see I mean, I guess at this point if there's proof about something, you know
There's proof, but it's like otherwise. I have I have some proof
No, no, no, I was just gonna say what do you think people would get the misunderstanding that it was you
I don't I don't get it right. I had proof of German lady because she knows I don't like her and I was
In the chat right before all that stuff happened
So she's lumping me in with it on purpose.
Hmm. That sounds like chinchilla. That was weird.
To you, um...
I don't know
No, it's because I overheard earlier you like I don't like spunky like you you how well do you like no
No, or I don't know I've been telling everyone this this is just never my
Instinct a page of my instinct and it's just from observations over the last couple months
And it's just going in the last week or two whatever
Really something wrong with this girl
But she's not what she seems to be and I don't mean about her real life
Work, I mean just the way she carries on I know I figure she's not like that
Got him or you need him
I do want to address something is that so this woman named
No, I want to I want to address something, please
I want to actually address
Something if you will let me if you allow me one second one second
Hi Sponky. Hey Spunk. How's it going? I like Sponky. Because, well, I just have to admit something. Is that okay? Like everybody? Like, I want to admit something. I'm, I'm gay.
No, I'm not dating you at all right now because oh my god putting you're putting up with what
she's doing and that makes me upset what oh my god
I might put you in a lot of ruin.
That was my last shot, that was my last shot.
So, take up, take up for your shit, take up for your shit.
The thing that is, the thing that is,
work things out or just talk, what happened,
what's going on here, is there a misunderstanding?
There's nothing to work out, I'll say it right now,
I'll leave her alone, I won't say another word about her.
But this lying about me being a doctor, it's just, that can't stand.
Well, I hear you up here running your mouth, admitting that you have no idea who I am or what I'm about,
and that you don't like me because of my body language and because of some conversations I've had with other people on panel.
No, no, I said body language is an indicator, but it's usually by behavior.
Yeah, and my behavior has been being nice to people who are nice to me.
Yeah, I know, and I think it's fake.
But some people are nervous when they're on camera on panels. It's not always. Maybe you
And if if if German lady was into me then I wouldn't get
Yeah, and yeah, why would I not think that you were part of the people talking me when you're heckling me and saying shit and then the next thing
I know
Why would you not think that because you didn't do it
You're lying again, you're lying again. You talk that's sick stop talking
All these girls think that they just can't talk all the time
Well, I'm not a dummy. Hey, I'll sue you. Let them talk it out. I'll sue you. I'll sue you. I'll sue you
That's funny.
Apparently, you've already admitted that you know that I
didn't, that I was involved in the thought process.
No, I have never admitted that.
I'm still running my mouth, and so you are a part of it.
So Bita is lying.
OK.
So you're calling Bita a liar.
We got that straight.
We, yeah, I did not say you were not a part of it, but I have not acknowledged anything
like that. I have no liar. You didn't tell me what happened in the chat. She's a liar. No,
she didn't tell her. I told her she's a liar. But if you're saying you're not a part of it and
you know, I've been saying that for the last two days, I've said it right to you and you're just
Little girl
So you're admitting that that you're jacketing me for no reason, right?
I'm admitting that you have been an asshole to me. Yeah, yeah, I admit I've been an asshole to you too. That's fine. That's fine
That's a given. That's a given. But you're admitting that you're jacketing me without proof, right?
You're jacketing me without proof, correct?
Correct? You're a disgusting liar, as I've said all along, correct?
So you have proved me right. Thank you very very much.
I have no fucking problem with you.
aside from you being an asshole.
Who is me? Sorry, Kate. It's me.
Hold on.
It's fine, Kate. Hi, it's me.
I never said that thing that is was not a part of it.
So now he's saying that I'm calling you a liar.
Is that okay with you?
Is it okay with you?
If you just read what you wrote to me?
Spunky
She said she said can you read what you wrote to her? Is it okay if you read?
I mean is it okay if I send it to Psyche and then he'll read what you wrote to me
So you kind of maybe that way think and see what you said to me in regards to that is that okay?
I write Psyche a letter or two while you read it because I'm not gonna be sitting here
I'm not gonna be called a liar
That's not what happened at all.
You can just like, just read it, just read it.
It's not a big deal.
Yeah, just read it, hurry.
Just read it.
It's like a song, just read it, read it.
Yeah, maybe we'll figure out who really talks to you,
you know, I don't know.
Yeah, and maybe you'll get a smile whenever you read what I say.
I am.
You son of a...
I'm just gonna say that I'm trying to tell the thing that I'm not lying, like I'm not
saying spunky sense.
I don't know what...
I'm not saying...
I'm not saying you're lying, Bita.
She's saying you're lying.
No, she's not.
She's saying that.
Why doesn't she believe that it might be you
because you antagonized her?
And that's exactly what she wrote to me,
but she said, I don't think it's him.
Read it.
Okay, I don't think it's him.
So there it is, right there. She admitted she doesn't think I'm the doxxer.
I mean, you can like, I just can't pretend like I'm the doxxer.
Yeah, there, there you go.
She made, she made it work.
She said, she made it work.
I promise you think didn't dox you.
She she promised me that and said she said hate that people confuse us when we're trying to chill
And I said he may not have been the one who actually did it, but he definitely added to it and encouraged
Wait, wait, can you can you take the key out because we can't hear what she's saying. Okay. Yeah
He's over her like let her read. I encouraged you being docs. Hey, I encouraged it. Did I tell you to say you're a doctor?
Did I, did I do that? Did I encourage you? Hey, wait, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
No, I don't want to say the name, but D-O-U-G, I mean, you don't have to say the name, but I don't want to say the name.
No, I don't want to say the name.
To me, that was clear, that was clearing his name, saying, I don't think he did it.
Like, that's what you said, like, Spunky.
So, I'm not saying, I even said, like, things can get confusing on the panels, you know, but...
You're admitting it, Spunky.
pretty freaking plain as day. You didn't even know I'm freaking like, I'm just trying to say, I'm not a freaking liar, but I said that to me and I was like, you are admitting it. So I am correct that you are a disgusting liar.
No, I don't think she's a disgusting liar. I think she's saying, I think she's just saying that she doesn't think that it's you, but she might have thought it's you because the way you talk to her like this, you know.
But to me that
Like when I say tough
They don't get they don't get a jacket. Well, maybe something so JT I don't know about that
I like spunky. I think um it gets listen um when I first like so-called god dogs people
thought they had information all this stuff but what I'm trying to say I'm not a liar when I got
the message I was like okay spunky say you know she doesn't think it's you it might have been other
people but you were antagonizing her so she might have thought that you had involvement with it and
that's pretty much what you wrote
Well, what's antagonizing? Doubting that she's a doctor? That's antagonizing?
Well, no, you're saying you just said you think she's disgusting and like being normal?
So what?
Who gives a fuck? Is she that special, that precious, that no one is allowed to think she's disgusting?
You asked me what you, I think what antagonizing is, and that's what I was saying, but I don't think...
Have a good night, man. Have a good night.
I don't know. Maybe...
I want you, you can clear it.
But why are you calling her disgusting? What makes her disgusting for you?
Look at what she's done!
What did she do?
What? Oh, German lady, you know exactly what she did.
No, I don't!
I really don't
What did she do you haven't been paying attention and i'm not going through it
I already went through it
Ziggy you need to fucking stop talking about me call me liar bullshit this and not i'm pretty much as
I don't like you either. I don't
Dude, I would chat too much. We don't have to like each other, but you don't have to mention my name every fucking two minutes
Uh, you're gonna have to fucking get a little bit better than that.
I'm not gonna change for you, okay?
I wanna see you fucking tell him that he is awesome.
Say it, say it, say it, say it, no, say that he is awesome.
Shut the fuck up, I don't fucking tell you stuff.
No, you don't tell me to shut the fuck up.
You tell him that fucking he's awesome.
He's better.
Who?
You tell Psyche that he's better than me.
Psyche is fucking awesome.
I love Psyche, he knows that.
No, I just want to know something. Spunky. Are you there? Okay. I want you to know this. I don't think I think it's almost like a whole misunderstanding.
do you do you believe in your heart that he did do this like you know what i'm
saying or do you have proof of it because that's really where it gets down to
you know i have no proof who did it who did it exactly so
i know what you're talking about why would i think anyone was vlogging on and then that came out
She said no proof of it. If you can think I'm disgusting
I think she thinks that you know because she can't figure out who else would be
Woman-mission the fucking
Listen, me and things don't have the same opinion about Spongebob.
I'm good.
I like her.
It doesn't matter.
It's over.
She's admitted.
He's admitted.
I don't need a doctor.
It's over.
She lied.
I'm good.
You're not.
She fucking completely lied.
Stupid.
I think Ziggy you're really confused and lost in this whole conversation.
You're dumb.
I don't like you.
Hey, hey, hey, I mean, it's just like that's just like no just like name-calling. Okay, let's not let's not go there
Let's say let's talk logically. Okay, or I'm calmly I want to kind of keep it cool. I want to like
It was we're making progress. I think with a lot of the stuff and it's like I think
It's not I don't even listen I shouldn't even have tried to like resolve the freaking issue. I really thought like
It wasn't fair what was happening because when I talked to him I felt like, you know, he does he was worried about
You know the allegations. It's like kind of
It's not cool. Like it's not fair. It wasn't fair.
Meaning not liking her and being mean to her is doesn't fucking matter.
That happens everywhere across all.
It's what he does. I think I think ridiculous.
I think thing has a crush on spunky.
No, no, it's seriously how she works, man.
I mean, why otherwise? Why do you hate her so much?
I don't get it.
You ever just get.
I got feeling like I don't know what to tell you.
LAS, after that you can start cuss me out, OK?
No, I've got feeling it's real simple.
It sounds like butterflies in your stomach, dude.
No, come on, man.
I'm not a frickin' schoolboy, man.
Let's stop this, please.
It's real simple.
It's it's her yacking and then fucking she's trying to fucking be friends in front of everybody
Fucking with his friends and then fucking. Oh, yeah
Yeah, she's a fucking bitch man fuck her
You talking a spunky or beta, I don't get it. I'm talking about beta
Raid is GT still there
Um, he's occupied right now. Why?
Spunky spunky, how long you knew JT? I'm just I just want to throw this question out
Now we cook
JT dots is in his community you are I know you know about that so I know you know about that spunky. She doesn't care
I
JT was
To be a wrench to be a mod as Bucky said no problem here
I see I see everything
JT is a weirdo. God is a weirdo rain is a other weirdo
If we're crying it sounds like you're obsessed with us Docs and spunky
Why would you bring up?
Oh, I've seen it with my own two eyes
What's your point?
What's your point? Nobody's lying about it
We cookin see
See they want to judge you they want to judge you think that is lying on you why they got everyone over there
The thing is, JT only docks it to people that do deserve it.
JT got a child
1865 I would like it. Yikes JT dots kids on his community wall. I support that
You forgot you had to apologize to me for calling me your little
You forgot you had to apologize to me. You forgot that I'll keep all my clips
You stupid piece of shit. I don't know
I don't want you to respect me fucking weirdo. You're probably
cancer survivors. That is no way you can never say that every time I get.
Fuck you. You want to fix it with you.
I'm not even. You fucking weird.
You know, I'm fix with you.
Go back and play your games.
I'm going to try to use psych.
Try to make you go out with two viewers.
I'm going to go out with two viewers.
OK, why are you so pressed about it?
You're weird. You're weird.
Why are you so pressed? Why are you so pressed about it?
You're weird.
Boom boom boom boom boom boom. What does that mean?
Dude, I'm gonna fix you. We're doing by the way. If anybody wants JT's gaming channel. It's JT gaming
Yeah, he needs to help he needs to help
share it in the link
Interested yeah, he needs to help
Was chicken if anybody was chicken I butcher them boom boom. Yeah, Ziggy's the chicken guy
All right, so lose your no disrespect to you thing that is I'm just saying no disrespect to you spunky
I'm just fucking I like to pick and choose but JT is the biggest weirdo. Hey JT acts as fun
Can I get a red he doesn't even do what he does? Hey, you can have a wrench and
He's got his boy
The word oh God these are the word oh, we know about why wouldn't why wouldn't they why'd you got to be wrench?
Being a rancher don't have why wouldn't they be right? Oh, hey, I'm your friend. Let me rent you. Hey
This guy sounds so
Oh, but Sparky, I'm not giving a fuck about you, but you lying on other people why are you fucking with the doctors yourself?
Your shit is going down on the world, you lied you lied about things that is right talking about he doctor
He didn't doctor. I was reading that whole chat. He didn't did that at all
Hey, I'm not even going I mean you did say I doxed you that's what you say that
And you've retracted you've retracted all the way back
People you fuck without you
In the brain
Bunky when you fly when you fly
When you fly close to the sun, you might get burnt.
I'd rather you stand down,
because the people you fuck with docks a lot of people.
Spunky, you know that, so chill out.
Range is a minute.
Spunky don't care, Spunky don't care.
Range just said it, so relax, Spunky.
You put in jackets on people
where your people docks kids on all that shit.
It's over, dude.
Exactly.
You think I don't know?
I do my homework before I take the link.
It's over.
It's over. I think baby's trying to say there's hypocrisy going on.
It's a lie. Exactly. I don't have beef with Spunky either, but I see.
I like Spunky and I hope that thing and Spunky can figure it out and work it out.
I honestly do. I don't have beef with Spunky.
I'm done with it. It's cleared up. It's done.
Okay, good. I didn't do it. Well, see, but when I left, um, you guys were saying I was lying. You
said like, so you're saying beta is lying. No, I wasn't lying to you, man. You gotta listen,
beta, because I was saying that you that to spunky, you've already admitted that I didn't do it.
And she was denying it. And I was saying, Oh, so you're saying beta beta is a liar because you're
Beedah she just let it go, beedah it wasn't on him, it was on spunky
Now he's saying it, now he's saying it
Individualist mother fucker, say ass again man, say it
Who that, Vicky? Who's that?
No, who that? Who that?
Who that, that's Vicky?
It's jam
Are you an ass?
That's straight team booting, they coming out
It's jam
Who that?
Let me hear that, let me hear that, let me hear that, let me hear that, let me hear that, let me hear that, let me hear that, let me hear that, let me hear that, let me hear that, let me hear that, let me hear that, let me hear that, let me hear that, let me hear that, let me hear that, let me hear that, let me hear that, let me hear that, let me hear that, let me hear that, let me hear that, let me hear that, let me hear that, let me hear that, let me hear that, let me hear that, let me hear that, let me hear that, let me hear that, let me hear that, let me hear that, let me hear that, let me hear that, let me hear that, let me hear that, let me hear that, let me hear that, let me hear that, let me hear that, let me hear that, let me hear that, let me hear that, let me hear that, let me hear
I know you now
JT shot when we got two viewers
Jan is Ziggy's woman actually
Yeah, his link share his link share his link
Oh, you don't got a wrench
Oh
Y'all go around hold on y'all go around
Say can I get a wrench Goddy Goddy
Jay actually for rent
For wrenches, I never asked for a wrench never
You never ask for a wrench or you never ask.
The word is ask.
Ask.
Hey bro, wrench me please.
Hey I'm J.J. Spunky.
Spunky.
You cool with me right Spunky?
Roger Rabbit.
Motherfucker.
Wrench me.
Please.
Imagine being so pressed about a wrench.
Wrench me.
Great to meet you.
Imagine having a face that looks like somebody sent you a cat-eye.
So, what are you doing, man?
He looks like you're a cat-eye.
Shout out to you, Sight.
Shout out to German lady.
Shout out to Bita.
Shout out to you, Spunky.
I don't got beef with you, but you call him.
You're going to be with me?
I'm going to be with you.
I know they will call you out too spunky
I gotta be with you
I gotta be with all of you
That's not what I'm talking about
It's on his community
I'm just saying I know you
Everybody stand up
I love you
Talk to everybody
Oh, don't go. Don't go. I got
What a fucking bald weirdo.
There goes, there goes Tim, man.
All right.
The dude with the camera on, man.
He's a good dude. I like him, man.
Who are you? I'm gonna add you.
I'm just a dude. Like, seriously, that's what my name means.
Yeah, me too, man.
I'm adding you, dude.
Yeah. Fucking your cold dude.
We're going to backing
Yeah, I think yeah
What is that? What's up to you guys to decide?
That's a dog. That's a dog. Oh
It's my little stinky. She's been scratching at the door this whole time. It's like a weird owl. Okay. No, and we're taking care of
psyche
My German lady. Hi
German lady. Good to see you. Hi, German lady
German
For the record, I like salmon. I think he's a cool guy. He's just he's just passionate. He's just very passionate. Oh, here's he's a weirdo
Oh, I like it. I like him too. I love the way he says
Well, I like German well German lady can speak I haven't seen you German lady in a bit. How are you?
I'm doing fine. I'm doing fine. I'm just enjoying my summer today. I was just randomly catching the stream
I was listening to
She hasn't been around in a while
And I was like, okay, let me let me go up
Good to see you. Oh dude, totally
How long have you guys known each other?
What do you mean? She's she's been on JT's panel before I know but how long how long have you guys known each other I?
Know for a few months a month. Oh shit like maybe maybe six or seven months. Maybe oh shit
What would I know of them because I listened to Jarl
That's my guilty pleasure, yeah, I've known I think I've known you for
Wiggins Wiggins is the old weirdo
right where she is and he meant Billy that's the cute of the year
right yeah the billy and wiggins fights oh my gosh
I've known her for probably
Dermal lady. I just want to say you know how I know Jar Wiggins and his family
He poses his community wall jars kids, which he still has on his community wall JT posted
On his community wall
Jarl
Right, right
Yeah, that's right now with with J
German lady, I'm like what like all JT did was recycle the Docs. That's it
Right. Yeah, and fucking Sam and you need to calm down with that fake-ass
Righteousness because don't even act like you give a shit about jar of wiggins and fucking dog
The fossil and the warts
You don't give a shit about this people. It's just one thing for you to fucking say about somebody else
People that I like so fuck off
What's up clumsy?
Clumsy my boy
Love clumsy man. Hold on ever. Oh, he just redo a dox by the way with a minor because oh
That shit is disgusting. So I'm gonna clip that good looking for that clip. Thank you. Salute
Oh, but he just redid it.
Congratulations, congratulations.
I'm going to cut that up.
Salute.
Thank you.
Oh, oh, we can hardly wait.
We can hardly wait.
This dude is weirdly obsessed with minors.
Very obsessed, very obsessed, like inappropriately obsessed.
Jump lady, where are you?
Okay, well, that's my cue. I said I was gonna come up here and say hi to y'all and say until he started shitting on me
So y'all have a good night. Hey, you have a good night too. See you, Jan
Yeah, I'm gonna joke down too, man. I'm gonna know new like for like what like
Nothing is gonna be resolved between you and and spunky nothing's gonna be resolved
No, I already said I'll lay off or I'm not gonna I'm not gonna go after or anything
But for me, I mean this whole thing's over
Anyway psych I'm gonna go. Thanks for having me up everyone
For those that I've just met
I guess everyone where you go like I think it's what like five years that I'm
What
No, no, no, you and I like was it five years and he was talking why
I
Might even hop back up later. I just I gotta go to have a smoke
Everyone take care. Ciao
Chow chow, let's suck in Ziggy Ziggy. Why does your picture look like a dick in balls?
Vegetables
Yeah, that's my vegetables dude, and they're fucking fertilizer and that's the side fucking free. Oh
Yeah
Do you hear it?
Yeah, we hear your chickens.
That's a loud mouth, man.
What are you doing to them, Ziggy Poms?
They walk free?
I'm clean now.
He's just a big mouth.
Beer-raised chicken, okay.
So, no, really...
Well, wait a minute. Look, like if we're being against racism and stuff someone is calling someone a monkey. That's
Why me and like can I call him a chicken?
Who's calling? Who's saying that? I'm so sorry. Hold on.
Go choke a chicken, Ziggy. Go choke it. Go choke it.
I mean, can I be like, yeah, you're nothing, but, you know,
I mean, it's no secret that you means a racist.
Right.
Yeah. Like, what if I come up to somebody and I'm like, yeah,
you know better than a chicken.
Well, that's not very good. She she calls people monkeys flying monkeys and shit like that like
But she called her a monkey like without the flying so that's yeah, but you know, you know, just well, you know
You guys didn't you have on the on the CFF wasn't that you're like, you know the title of the thing was like a little circus
Ted, what is CFF?
Well, yeah, it was to poke at you know, you me calling us monkeys, you know flying monkeys.
Oh, well, yeah
I just don't want to make it everything a racial thing like I don't think that she's
But she is racist though. She has said things about Jews. She doesn't like you Jewish people
Okay, well, yeah
She's you know, she's is long
and but you know i'm a minority like you know like there's a lot of minorities like let's like
that's why it's like and even even i'm not gonna i'm not gonna say and name names but even the
girl that i was suggesting that would name she i mean she offended she offended ld because he's
She was praising she was praising Hitler one time and you know
Well, she was praising that guy and you know LD didn't like that shit like he got met at her for that
Like I don't like I'm just letting you know
I
Actually saw it live when
LD had his
Seizure when he had his famous seizure. Oh, yeah
That was bad. Do you still have the video?
because i can't find the video i used to have in 2021 i had like a clip channel for ip2 it got
terminated but i don't have it man i clipped all the good good time stuff when ember and
The last time that happened, the last time you had a, you know, an incident, um, he was dealing with a lot of stuff. So it was understandable.
I mean, his father was dying, you know, like he was passing away. Yeah.
It was horrible.
German lady, it was good as you.
Okay. Well, okay.
who's who's who just left me see so there's German lady okay okay yeah I'm sorry I've got a lot
going on right now I'm sorry if I'm a little distracted what's happening what's wrong no
I'm just kidding I'm there's just some stuff going on and other stuff too I'm getting just
stuff going on we're all good I think it's out of the chicken though it sounds like a nice healthy
screaming, quacking. I call it quacking, called loudmouth.
Okay, and by the way, and it's like even if like
People are banned from the chat like it's like you know the chat. Oh you ban me from the chat or something
No, no, no, no, nobody's banned from the chat like nobody's been there might be
You know
Run the chat, but it's like if you if you we already said that you ban me from a chat
Well, I mean it's like I'm bad everybody last night. Okay, so
Plus a few days ago, too. I everyone's unbanned so well
Did did you or you impressed like that I stood up for you for better?
No, no, no, no, this is like that. I mean
Come on, man. I'm like on your team. I'm on your team
Okay, look, you know
I just don't I don't have a I wanted you to get out your side of the story and everything
I don't want to be taking sides. There's a I'm trying to stay
You know, it's slightly mutual place as a host and everything and like I want people to be getting along
We said I want people to come to understanding
That's the problem. Yeah, I'm I'm glad we came to an understanding psyche and you didn't just ban me like just like that
You know and and it's like, you know and guys like the policy from now on will be if someone's bothering you in the chat
You know everybody there's like if you click on the name you can block because it's like it's not
I'm not talking about mods. Exactly. I block people. Yeah, you can block people in the chat
You don't have to see any of their comments. I don't have one
Okay, so
Oh, yeah, how do I block people in the chat? I don't know.
If you click on the name, it will just block it for you, Ziggy.
Oh, you mean like block block? I thought you meant like, hey, I have a hammer and I can...
No, no, no, no, no.
Oh, right. Gotcha. Yeah, you're not giving us equipment. Got it.
Well, you know, I'm... Well, you know, it's like, it doesn't really...
It doesn't really matter at this point, it's like, it's like because I'm
Oh, it does matter, it's like
I don't want to, I don't want, I don't want, by the way, mods, I don't want any
I don't, I don't want, I kind of want to do that
It's just like
No, no, no, I don't, I kind of want to do that
You can time out, people can be timed out, like
What do you mean? Like, I kind of want to do that
Like, I kind of want to be like
Oh, no, you can't do that
Yeah, well, it's like, you know
Come on
Why are you worried? I'm sure he's not even reading the chat. Why are you worried about the chest?
German lady she knows it. She's my favorite woman
Hey quiet because you know, it's always it's better to
To learn to get along. Okay, because it's like if I block you, you know, they're just gonna be people cut
You know people are just gonna come on under different names and it's gonna be like, you know, it's not gonna be
I don't want the monsters playing whack-a-mole all day. It's like unless there's something seriously against the rules
I'll put the rules up on the screen, too
Yeah, but no no no no wait wait. Can I I want to say one more thing about German lady?
Although, that she is the wonderful tyke, I don't know what she's saying.
You say, Wonderbar.
No, Wonderful.
Fucking, she is watching the fucking most retarded shit in the world.
Okay, well, can someone give Siggi like a pack of crayons or something for like an hour?
We have a we have a guest we have a guest appearing in the studio one second
Let me just make sure that they're gone. There it goes. Hello. No, it's me. It's me. It's me
Who's me?
First of all
I never asked Mr. I never here comes the racists to have this the hammer on history because I'm the outsider and
For being a racist
Why
Go ahead
Whenever you know what you do, I know what I know what exactly do we do
Yeah, you guys you guys doxing people remember
Yeah, I already admitted to that. I mean JT, JT's on the doza, JT's on the doza. I never denied it.
Okay?
I never denied it. JT, JT's on the doza. I never denied that.
To be nice like you. I never pretending.
You always pretend to be nice, but secretly you are a racist. You are a racist.
He's not boxing he's taking a picture from somebody that already put the picture up. He's that's not a Docs
Okay
Doxing people address
Doxing people how that was me. I did that
That's the FF do
The circus friends forever. That's you guys do
People address
People house
Call it that good. Is that a good thing? No, you already gave out the address and then
Know what you did
This whole time. Oh, what did you do this time Ziggy? I'm she put her look at you guys
Because because you guys stream kind of empty
We don't have to stream all the time you're weird
Yeah, since since you your stream is empty rain so what so we don't care
We don't care about streaming
We don't care about viewers
and streaming and all that bullshit
Don't lie, don't lie
I'm watching, I'm learning
Don't lie
You need to learn better English then
Well you won't know
My English is not my manner language
Why?
Look at you
Because you don't get
You don't get a lot of things people say to you you you using YouTube more than 20 years more than 20 years
I'm many years. What are you talking about? I met you. I'm making a beautiful piano chat room
I'm yeah a few years ago not fucking 20 years. You're weird. Don't lie
Don't lie. Don't lie
There's the accident she makes no sense
she makes no sense no logic no no sense normal people already know who you are
you jt good good who's your body don't forget about godi don't forget about godi don't forget
about godi who's your people yeah mr godi yeah so what is your people who's your people
Is it you guys?
No, we actually have almost 20 people
That's funny
Yeah, I don't know why people are so pressed about discord or discord
You think that dude, do you know what we do in discord sometimes like my woman will like bake a cake be a woman
Your woman
Maybe you can be a woman for me
Mr.. Ziggy stop simping
You want to come to discord. No, thank you
I never hang out until with the abnormal people. Okay? Oh
They don't have a job they don't have a good things to do. No, don't have a job. Sorry. No, sorry
She said you don't have a job Ziggy. Oh
Wow
Yeah, he's a farmer chicken farmer. I am right. Yes, sir. That's why that's why you love chicken. Yes, sir
You say you say mister I say yes sir. This is not the Hollywood train. Yes sir. You know how acting to be sweet to be nice maybe pretending
Don't pretend
What do you what do you I don't pretend to be nice I am nice until like, you know
You pretending to be nice with me
No, you be nice to me and I'll be nice to you
No, I don't I don't I don't have time to be uh to be nice to you rain
What do you have time? I don't care about you. You me you care about JT. You like you're always talking him
You're always talking JT
Mr. Aldi you're always talking JT everywhere he goes
And you were stalking
You're stalking ld
Excuse me
You were all up in his panels and shit, being a whore, taking off your heat job, putting on makeup.
The only woman like Jethie is you.
Oh.
I was talking about LD like you go up in his panels without make with makeup on without your heat job
You're you're a fucking whore. What is that? Is that not racist? So what I don't I don't want you
Accident
And then you're hiding I'm telling your husband. I'm telling you still there. I'm telling you up on YouTube. I'm telling George
Okay
I'm telling your husband. You don't know my husband. You don't know I'm telling George Arc. Yeah, I'm telling your you don't know my husband
That's acid Crip Cloning has my husband acid trip. Okay husband. Holy stop rain stop
Do not many pull wait wait wait wait I don't like
Next victim by the same
Remember that. Holy shit. I don't talk to people with broken English
Oh my god, yeah
I hope you give me a pass. I hope you give me a pass. Hey rain. Hey rain
Miss Phoebe know who you are
Okay, no
My team buddy. What are you? What are you doing? You're crazy. Are you crazy? I never miss miss the psyche
Did I ever asking you to give me the hammer to protect me? No
That's that's miss Jamie recommended. Oh, yeah, but you're gonna be outside. That's the sucky thing
That's I am nobody, but I am someone. Oh
Unlike you rain you keep pretending
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
things are going to be mad i don't care why i don't care when mr or mr sycan his people calling me a racist
but i have my point you're talking about yesterday
so you admit to being a racist okay so yeah i'm not lying i'm not lying i did it i call someone
So you called them the N-word with a hard R?
Is that okay? I don't understand. I don't understand.
This person has a member.
That's not okay.
And he keeps insulting the society in front of people?
I don't go on panels with racists, sorry.
Look, sweetie, I don't know you that well,
but you don't want to be judged.
I'm done.
Later.
You don't want to be judged for your religion.
Yeah, please go, CFS.
Don't don't don't borders. Mr. Sike and friends
I'm a free now. I'm okay without the hammer. I'm okay. I'm okay with with the time out
I'm okay because I'm the outsider. I'm not even American
Listen to it
I'm Asian everyone to be able to talk on the panel and it's like unless someone breaks the panel rules when they're on the panel
It's a different
Different she was chat, you know the chat the mother she birth control over I have control the panel and
She break she break the rules. I'm totally okay. This is easy. I'm not speaking. This is like a tension because
I'm like a new, I'm not a new person for him, maybe the pendulum might fix all this, I don't know.
Okay, we have just Dean coming up, hold on one second, I've just seen in the back one second.
Hey!
This is me. I'm just letting you know that this is a little really religious tactic that this oh my god
uses one of
People because I know because I have done religion and I had no that this is a technique that fucking you me use this
Because I don't know anything. I'm just so innocent. I'm not from this world
I don't know what I'm doing. I'm just a little, you know, I don't know what it is. I don't know what bread is buttered in. I'm a little flour, and I'm not from this country, and I don't know what I'm saying.
Yeah, right, bitch.
Wow.
Bye, grandma.
Oh my God.
That was wild.
Wow, that was what okay, mr. Ziggy, you know miss Justin you guys hang out together
I remember everything
Don't act. This is not the Hollywood.
What are you going to do now?
This is the psyche stream.
Stop manipulate.
Stop manipulate people.
Put it in there. What are you going to do?
Put it in the dish.
Be real mr. Diggy. Where are you? I am what are you gonna do? Stop pretending? Stop pretend
No pretending at all. You did
Skimping you already have your your women
In my opinion he does that too. Hi ma'am. Hi miss nice to meet you. Yeah, you mean from from a walker walker land
What?
Yeah
I don't know why you're taking shots at me now. I'm being nice to you. So I don't know where this aggression is coming from
I never I never I
Think I was on YouTube since like
2019 on September and I never pretending to be nice or to be kind to people when
why not yeah I mean I mean you know a lot of people it was like I always I
always been on cam because I have a like
You know like a worse like a worse situation. They keep calling. Oh, you mean oh you mean with the week
Oh, you mean you're wearing a week. That's not your your real hair or everything there and then I decide
trolling
Yeah, I
Okay, I
Decide to okay who tried to uh, I mean who tried to uh
May I'm missing a round with me?
I would play the game too. That's that's what I that's what I did then who messed around with you
Mr. Ziggy
What do you want?
Who messed around what did you do to miss beta now you try to do around with you who mr. Psyche?
Hmm. No, I'm asking you what you gave to this beta. I heard what you did
My German lady was talking to you first
Why why you you always cause a problem on people panel why I was on I was on
Mr. Brian black yesterday I was on Miss Marisa yesterday
Can you can you have a
People panels who were coming you talk to the woman
Why are you here why not working?
Dr.. He's a farmer. He is working kind of I
Will I won't let mr. Psyche
Feel sad because of you guys see FF, okay
Just because he always nice to all of you don't think don't don't think that you guys can
Manipulate can control his panel. No, don't
Don't you don't do that. Do you like my picture?
Love it
Answer me. This is like answer me mr. Ziggy
Yes, I
So funny when rain saying that I am anti-semitic
She's so funny and she's really funny. That's what I'm saying. I talked I think I think I I'm okay with mr.
LD now even we don't talk like before he didn't and they keep saying oh you mean it's
anti-semitic what that's funny that's really funny the newest people not only mr. Mr. LD that I met
There's a like a five Jewish and I'm okay with that
So so am I anti-Semitic? No, am I anti Chris? No
No
Well, I think that German lady was talking to you
You try to get the heat on me, I see what you're doing here.
Yeah, I mean, people, I'm sure that kind of people like the CFF don't have much attention in real life.
That's why they come to, yeah, Mrs. Digi.
You know, Digi.
No, I
It's like it was like
Keep saying I'm in this
Attack of the new crew now, okay
Yeah, the new crew. I've heard the new crew, but I've never heard the CFF. I don't know what that is
Don't lie, Mr. Ziggy
Don't lie. Why do you do? Don't lie. You know what is you know, really you know what they don't
I'd work. I don't know. Don't lie. Don't lie. Don't lie. Don't
After the new crew as a ff and then what else I don't know
Yeah, it's like a someone said that my job is a fake has a teacher. I think I have a you are
Yeah, you are a fake teacher. I have enough proof and then
Someone mentioned. Oh, yeah
No, no, no stop
Was that really your teaching that was your that was your class? Yes. I am a teacher
Holy shit, I teach you with the good
Oh, no, you don't understand
Whenever she did that like it was I did I did I was drunk too and but anyway
Insane like that wouldn't happen in America. You're you're class
Well, you're not teaching anything because I only saw a fucking like sick desk
I'm not teaching anything
I'm sure that on my channel, I have a lot of proof about my job, my life.
Yeah, but it looked like trashy.
Did you check it? Did you check it? No.
I mean, whenever you were trying to do that.
Even from life, even from life to me, did you check it? No.
I'm not picking if it would be good. I would say the CFF crew only judging, judging, judging and judging.
No, dude, buddy, I fucking go camping and shit and like, oh, you know, shower in the fucking water and do whatever.
But that looks like fucking crazy.
You already have a woman but you keep shimping to another woman.
That's right. I do everything you don't
We're making progress she's laughing no, we're making progress
You're making Farmer?
Well, she's actually...
You don't even know this.
But like, she...
No, but she's actually like...
We know each other.
Like, you make it sound like we're having
like an intimate kind of stuff going on.
Oh, yeah. I know.
Right now.
You're trying to get me in trouble, yeah?
Both of you are trouble-struck.
Ma'am, I will, I will making you laugh.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah.
What else?
Why are you doing a good job?
Where did she go?
Ray, where did she go?
You're doing a good job.
Yeah, I'm doing a good job, and I'm proud.
I'm not a teacher's lie.
I'm not.
I'm not
They call me has a feature of lies. No, I'm not
Yeah, when it's funny when
have a I have a bat I have a bat well you need to go and get a budget that's
what you need huh I think you're saying whenever you say that I gotta go you
gotta get a budget let her finish then go yeah I this is for mr. psychic it's
And I take it, I take it, I take it the consequence, so it's fine, it's fine, and that's so fine.
She's going to win, she's going to win.
She's going to win if he asks you, if he asks you specifically to be ready.
No, no, he never asked me, he never asked me, and then he kept being attacked by that person.
I just hate it, just to, yeah, he called Mrs. Sike, he had the skinny one and everything.
Why I mean
What is she talking about?
Now this is what happened why I've been called
Dude, you don't nothing. This is the gear. Let me finish. I gotta go and stop working
Listen, um, Mr. Sike, thank you for always welcoming me and I hope
Yeah, I hope the CFF do not
Doing bad things
to you again and again and
Just because I'm not a
I'm not on your and I'm not you're on your stream
and like uh before you know dude that's weird oh and by the way
i apologize did you shut up no i'm not going to by the way i hope i hope you
apologize you really like the attention so sorry you keep talking you keep talking
that's you you keep saying cff i'm not a part of this cff
That's weird. Don't lie.
You keep saying all kinds of weird shit.
I have all the truth, Mrs. D.
Go ahead. Show the proof.
Show where I'm at, see you up up.
Okay. Thank you, Mr. Psyche.
Ma'am, what is your name?
You have a great day, Chiaul.
She doesn't know.
You can call me Chiaul.
It's too small.
The name is the...
She doesn't do that
because she's smart.
No, thank you for you, Mr. Ziggy,
because I know who you are.
She's smart.
You're part of this BFS.
Okay?
Tirku's friends forever.
Put that hood on.
That's all, you guys.
Make sure you put that in the end, ma'am. Thank you. Bye
Put that
Productive
You are you did okay. You laughed a little
You were being a little fucked up though was teaching us and we're wiser than yeah, but you were also like yeah, you were also like
Ziggy, don't stop it, you are definitely you sound already wiser than you sounded like an hour ago
so it it helped she did help you yeah whatever
fuck it out there
what's up psyche oh i'm sorry he's looking on farmers only
I'm on only farmers right now. The only farmers looking at news is Ziggy with this.
Yeah, we farm dude. You didn't know that? You didn't know that we farm?
I know you do. I want some of your tomatoes. I want to try those and a chicken too.
Oh god. Oh dude, I'll send you some tomatoes man for like shipping free man.
Okay well I might have to go pick them up myself right?
Uh, yeah, there's a light. I might have to go pick them up. I don't know. I'm
But yeah, do you see the rainbows? I do have rainbows all around my room. What are you talking about?
What? Oh, no, I mean, it's like, no, I mean, I would instead of like shipping me a ticket. I'm asking German lady like, what are you talking about?
Rainbows
Good energy rainbows
Good energy
Yes, you know where I saw you I saw you in
Because they were mentioning discord that reminded me. I saw you in Wendy Peck's
Discord like a while ago. Yes, you know her. Yes, I've had her on the show. Oh, yeah
Oh, you mean are you talking about how the song?
Yeah
Yeah, so okay, so you know the other one, right?
Who?
who
He was wanting to bring her up on the goddamn fucking this shit
Elisa you're talking about yeah, of course, I know her I wasn't her to score to but for whatever reason
Why?
I'm friends with Elisa too. I was on her
When she before she started IRL, she had like a podcast kind of stuff going on like a panel like every now is like rotating panel.
I was up there one time too, like, you know, one time, but I can't I can't believe that you like you have all people I can't believe that you would have like me.
Yeah, I understand.
But holy shit.
What's up? What's up, Ziggy?
What are you saying?
What are you? Well, I know I know exactly who she is
Alyssa or Wendy or we're talking about Alyssa. Yeah, well both. Yeah. Yeah, okay. I love I love I love I love
Whatever I don't know I don't know her like that. That's not what I'm saying, but I did like whenever fucking that dude hit her
I mean, look, she was kind of asking for it, yeah.
She was like, okay, guys, again, again, again, let's, like, you know, just let's say, let's
move on.
Let's move on.
We're moving on.
Oh hi doggers dog this rule Dodgers rule daughter of what Dodgers rule, okay
I don't know guys. We don't want to I don't want to support any kind of you kind of violence. Okay, it's rude
He doesn't want to yeah
Okay, we are we are philanthropists. Oh
Casey, I know it's you, but I don't like yours
I don't like the name of your avatar or the name of your avatar if you change the avatar maybe I'll consider it Casey
But I don't like you know suck on my CAWK or whatever
Whoa, what happened here? That's what you know, Casey's at like there's not supposed to be bad words here
Yeah, I don't I don't want that
Right, yeah
Where has a German lady been? You've been sucking on
CEO and no words
Hush, huh, huh, or did hey
Said I have to it's an it's unedited. It's edited
Yeah, where you've been
Jamie's cowboys not race. I mean it's like can we like can we uh, let's
I like this. I kind of like this to be honest like it's like hey Jamie
Hey, you little bi
Yeah, it's edited like
The females on my show names, okay, I didn't edit I edited it
Well, she's she's like I mean it's people have different reactions. I don't I don't know
Hey, you little bi
Kind of like you like I like sometimes I think you're a little bi T old asterisk asterisk
You're gonna me
Yeah
Yeah, you said I have to edit everything come on. I didn't get to edit I'm saying
Respect the panel rules. Yeah, but I think you're you're being a little behind asterisk asterisk asterisk
Hey, what are you gonna call me? You're gonna call me names now. Okay. You are great
Yeah, but I'm not what am I gonna get kids?
What do you mean?
You're walking on thin ice there, Ziggy
Ziggy's in the green room for a little bit, you know
Don't push it. Don't push it. Don't push your luck, Ziggy. You know, it's like, oh, okay. Well, you know
I mean, I was gonna
Yeah, I'm dropping down. Um, nice talking to you guys
Don't ruin my exit Ziggy. Let me finish now to you. Oh, you better not be your this better not be your exit
Yeah, I come I come back another time
Appreciate you and you're you're thank you for being it like oh, dude
I'll be back another time. Thanks. She's like one of the most great people that I have fucking met and all of my fucking what
Knowing you're a good person. I hope you always it's Ziggler. It's Z. I know my shit's done
So now it's Ziggler 2
so
Or is it a one? Sorry
Later, thank you. Why'd you say love you? Like you don't love it. I do so
Hey, man quit waving your hand around like a BIT
Okay, so we are gonna wrap up for now. I might come back and test something
Let's play this out on a high note. It's like everyone's
Going other places and so no you check out different things. Oh wow look at the light show look at that
What like how about like how about some positive vibes? I don't know
I hope that I did okay. I tried. I just wanted everybody to get their their words out and stuff like that and
You know
Maybe I'm not perfect. I'm sorry if anybody's upset with me
You know sorry
to see the flame but envy was the price of fame and now he stands where the echoes fall
with tarot in hand hearing every call from praise to venom in the same breath said
but the fire in his eyes burns gold